team	O
india	B-LOC
kal	O
honay	O
pakistan	B-LOC
pakistan	B-LOC
crore	O
younis	O
kal	O
afridi	O
purana	O
hazar	O
england	O
tournament	O
spinner	O
bowling	O
coach	O
sab	O
psl	B-ORG
bura	O
halfcentury	O
ki	O
kiya	O
australia	O
pitch	O
spinner	O
aur	O
do	O
hazar	O
match	O
wicket	O
par	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
rahi	O
kal	O
islamabad	B-LOC
zyada	O
keh	O
ne	O
par	O
jo	O
england	O
ya	O
shoaib	O
chota	O
selection	O
jab	O
jo	O
magar	O
crore	O
shoaib	O
keh	O
lahore	B-LOC
jo	O
the	O
par	O
ka	O
acha	O
australia	O
series	O
magar	O
agar	O
keh	O
quetta	B-LOC
spinner	O
bahut	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
do	O
selection	O
peshawar	B-LOC
javed	O
do	O
rahe	O
kal	O
agar	O
player	O
ya	O
india	B-LOC
chota	O
zyada	O
yahan	O
woh	O
pitch	O
jo	O
islamabad	B-LOC
se	O
rahe	O
lakh	O
score	O
stadium	O
shoaib	O
team	O
maidan	O
player	O
fielding	O
nay	O
rahe	O
naseem	O
tab	O
tha	O
yeh	O
ab	O
keh	O
panch	O
acha	O
gaddafi	O
team	O
gaye	O
jab	O
misbah	O
crore	O
jeetnay	O
hazar	O
wasim	O
cricket	O
bara	O
pakistan	B-LOC
england	O
gaddafi	O
tab	O
sab	O
jeetnay	O
pakistan	B-LOC
hazar	O
india	B-LOC
fielding	O
stadium	O
gaye	O
wahan	O
team	O
batting	O
sab	O
ek	O
char	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
yahan	O
lahore	B-LOC
cricket	O
us	O
afridi	O
jab	O
stadium	O
lekin	O
bura	O
rizwan	O
opener	O
pakistan	B-LOC
t20	O
woh	O
char	O
the	O
lekin	O
lekin	O
shaheen	O
chota	O
lekin	O
world	O
par	O
naya	O
keh	O
kam	O
iqbal	O
tournament	O
player	O
halfcentury	O
league	O
hain	O
kuch	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
jeetnay	O
ab	O
pakistan	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
keh	O
match	O
shaheen	O
lekin	O
opener	O
match	O
batting	O
afridi	O
teen	O
gayi	O

tenure	O
agar	O
referendum	O
naya	O
siyasat	O
yahan	O
kiya	O
aur	O
party	O
yeh	O
jab	O
bara	O
political	O
parliament	O
pakistan	B-LOC
panch	O
bura	O
mein	O
karachi	B-LOC
jab	O
democracy	O
char	O
aur	O
char	O
assembly	O
bura	O
jama	O
nomination	O
aj	O
resign	O
ke	O
provincial	O
raha	O
jab	O
hukumat	O
jama	O
sab	O
bahut	O
ya	O
ke	O
ka	O
hai	O
is	O
naya	O
siyasi	O
intikhabat	O
raees	O
accountability	O
zilah	O
gaya	O
protest	O
pakistan	B-LOC
dissolution	O
raees	O
hain	O
democracy	O
ko	O
ne	O
mansoob	O
democracy	O
lahore	B-LOC
manifesto	O
tha	O
leader	O
keh	O
jo	O
wazir	O
democracy	O
bhutto	O
ne	O
senate	B-ORG
lahore	B-LOC
transparency	O
do	O
awam	O
government	O
senate	B-ORG
reform	O
ya	O
naya	O
tenure	O
premier	O
muariza	O
judiciary	O
magar	O
qanoon	O
policy	O
raha	O
wazeer	O
jama	O
judiciary	O
se	O
muariza	O
parliament	O
yahan	O
ab	O
raha	O
honay	O
muariza	O
rehbar	O
pakistan	B-LOC
campaign	O
adalat	O
hai	O
intekhab	O
election	O
nomination	O
ka	O
sau	O
wahan	O
sifarshi	O
hakumat	O
awam	O
gayi	O
hukumat	O
nazim	O
protest	O
political	O
ko	O
ilaqah	O
hukumat	O
nizam	O
imran	O
kam	O
campaign	O
political	O
hain	O
alliance	O
bhutto	O
thi	O
kuch	O
tenure	O
ya	O
honay	O
tanqeed	O
lakh	O
teen	O
acha	O
gayi	O
umeedwar	O
woh	O
sovereignty	O
kuch	O
insaf	O
ballot	O
nab	B-ORG
kam	O
kal	O
hain	O
se	O
kam	O
hakumat	O
kam	O
pta	O
pta	O
is	O
ke	O
legislation	O
yeh	O
rahe	O
judiciary	O
opposition	O
nawaz	O
parliament	O
ka	O
kuch	O
alliance	O
bahut	O
lahore	B-LOC
acha	O
to	O
jo	O
sab	O
policy	O

naya	O
saudi	O
sulah	O
to	O
woh	O
negotiations	O
phir	O
nuclear	O
baqiyat	O
ka	O
sco	B-LOC
turkey	B-LOC
islamabad	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
affairs	O
sco	B-LOC
zyada	O
muahida	O
keh	O
ab	O
council	O
yeh	O
bara	O
honay	O
agreement	O
bairoon	O
cooperation	O
lahore	B-LOC
purana	O
secretary	O
ko	O
aid	O
uae	B-LOC
sarhad	O
bahut	O
iran	B-LOC
rahi	O
tab	O
honay	O
magar	O
gaya	O
refugee	O
muahida	O
yeh	O
hazar	O
uk	B-LOC
diplomacy	O
phir	O
thi	O
bahut	O
treaty	O
raha	O
mein	O
intifada	O
aj	O
minister	O
ya	O
keh	O
humanitarian	O
state	O
talks	O
ek	O
the	O
bara	O
ne	O
visit	O
muahida	O
veto	O
hazar	O
sau	O
mein	O
sab	O
bairoon	O
alliance	O
char	O
ka	O
jangi	O
gayi	O
tha	O
tha	O
usa	B-LOC
yeh	O
ka	O
ek	O
summit	O
to	O
turkey	B-LOC
humanitarian	O
chota	O
tab	O
relations	O
nuclear	O
bahut	O
rahi	O
ab	O
rahe	O
turkey	B-LOC
kuch	O
agar	O
uae	B-LOC
ambassador	O
sab	O
embassy	O
zyada	O
uk	B-LOC
bara	O
kuch	O
aid	O
lakh	O
refugee	O
aqwam	O
ne	O
council	O
council	O
nuclear	O
crore	O
bhi	O
asean	O
lekin	O
bhi	O
foreign	O
par	O
aj	O
security	O
kam	O
tha	O
negotiations	O
mein	O
gaya	O
karachi	B-LOC
ke	O
oic	B-ORG
uae	B-LOC
mamlaat	O
bahut	O
affairs	O
ajlasa	O
lahore	B-LOC
sulah	O
ambassador	O
turkey	B-LOC
bainul	O
crore	O
lakh	O
trade	O
cooperation	O
negotiations	O
ka	O
karachi	B-LOC
uk	B-LOC
purana	O
ko	O
refugee	O
crore	O
karachi	B-LOC
conflict	O
ya	O
jab	O
crore	O
kuch	O
trade	O
roznamcha	O
muzakarat	O
char	O
is	O
char	O
summit	O
hai	O
sco	B-LOC
alliance	O
lekin	O
muahida	O
bara	O
ek	O
kal	O
ka	O
border	O
alatifaq	O
naya	O
security	O
sco	B-LOC
secretary	O
zyada	O
india	B-LOC
ki	O
foreign	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
un	O
jo	O
crore	O
char	O
kal	O
aqwam	O
chota	O
lakh	O
bahut	O
relations	O
diplomacy	O
border	O
do	O
intifada	O
muahida	O
muzakarat	O
honay	O
yeh	O
sco	B-LOC
treaty	O
magar	O
bairoon	O
usa	B-LOC
yeh	O

college	O
parhai	O
is	O
student	O
college	O
naya	O
bura	O
hain	O
ghar	O
lekin	O
education	O
ya	O
taleem	O
bara	O
ki	O
rahe	O
school	O
hospital	O
bahut	O
kuch	O
welfare	O
maternal	O
mortality	O
sanitation	O
bimari	O
ab	O
zyada	O
shelter	O
sabhyata	O
do	O
par	O
bahut	O
bachay	O
ngo	O
ke	O
clinic	O
woh	O
se	O
student	O
water	O
acha	O
school	O
bimari	O
tha	O
jo	O
dawa	O
islamabad	B-LOC
raha	O
par	O
sab	O
kuch	O
lekin	O
yeh	O
honay	O
gaye	O
aman	O
yahan	O
rehan	O
aj	O
hain	O
flood	O
hain	O
jab	O
ab	O
do	O
crore	O
panch	O
islamabad	B-LOC
bijli	O
welfare	O
poverty	O
dawa	O
woh	O
gaya	O
disease	O
honay	O
kiya	O
water	O
hai	O
lakh	O
aur	O
zyada	O
health	O
hazar	O
se	O
tab	O
purana	O
bara	O
surgery	O
sab	O
jo	O
lakh	O
teen	O
chota	O
rahe	O
panch	O
ngo	O
hai	O
doctor	O
medicine	O
aman	O
aur	O
sab	O
naya	O
taleem	O
who	B-ORG
gaya	O
sewage	O
vaccine	O
who	B-ORG
honay	O
teacher	O
taleem	O
ka	O
sarkardar	O
vaccine	O
keh	O
college	O
ghar	O
patient	O
agar	O
rahi	O
aman	O
ilaj	O
education	O
jab	O
shagird	O
bura	O
tha	O
diabetes	O
jab	O
student	O
teacher	O
wahan	O
keh	O
parhai	O
ki	O
sabhyata	O
malaria	O
aur	O
hazar	O
char	O
madrasa	O
purana	O
polio	O
poverty	O
scholarship	O
ya	O
sabhyata	O
islamabad	B-LOC
ke	O
literacy	O
shagird	O
bhi	O
nay	O
patient	O
tab	O
islamabad	B-LOC
patient	O
teacher	O
do	O
aur	O
aman	O
aur	O
college	O
chota	O
kitab	O
degree	O
acha	O
mein	O
karachi	B-LOC
parhai	O
medicine	O
lakh	O
aabadi	O
jo	O
mental	O
sewage	O
maternal	O
se	O
school	O
ab	O
jab	O
the	O
parhai	O
se	O
malaria	O
bachay	O
hain	O
community	O
nutrition	O
teen	O
us	O
flood	O
sau	O
islamabad	B-LOC
aur	O
kam	O
dengue	O
doctor	O
parhai	O
yahan	O
sau	O
school	O
sarkardar	O

kal	O
bahut	O
honay	O
ko	O
honay	O
the	O
poverty	O
bhi	O
honay	O
nay	O
keh	O
taleem	O
curriculum	O
community	O
bahut	O
kal	O
agar	O
ke	O
nay	O
tab	O
sab	O
rehan	O
flood	O
dengue	O
sab	O
honay	O
mental	O
lekin	O
cancer	O
nay	O
cancer	O
sanitation	O
scholarship	O
clinic	O
se	O
ilaj	O
mortality	O
ki	O
woh	O
aj	O
aj	O
sahan	O
vaccine	O
school	O
bimari	O
lahore	B-LOC
aabadi	O
bura	O
magar	O
to	O
agar	O
diabetes	O
zyada	O
diabetes	O
ne	O
ustaad	O
is	O
acha	O
yahan	O
covid	O
medicine	O
jab	O
se	O
honay	O
welfare	O
unicef	B-ORG
magar	O
ya	O
ngo	O
ya	O
jab	O
is	O
vaccine	O
ko	O
sanitation	O
taleem	O
covid	O
bahut	O
social	O
diabetes	O
ne	O
paani	O
mental	O
char	O
doctor	O
bara	O
par	O
bimari	O
chota	O
kam	O
kuch	O
paani	O
is	O
lekin	O
raha	O
curriculum	O
jo	O
vaccine	O
curriculum	O
thi	O
who	B-ORG
lahore	B-LOC
panch	O
ne	O
tab	O
community	O
pakistan	B-LOC
lakh	O
mortality	O
ghar	O
development	O
university	O
rehan	O
ghar	O
ke	O
student	O
honay	O
hai	O
zyada	O
zyada	O
dengue	O
literacy	O
qoum	O
paani	O
aj	O

saarc	B-ORG
ne	O
agreement	O
phir	O
tab	O
turkey	B-LOC
chota	O
ki	O
cooperation	O
yeh	O
oic	B-ORG
raha	O
minister	O
hazar	O
nato	B-ORG
russia	B-LOC
roznamcha	O
ke	O
islamabad	B-LOC
asean	O
tha	O
aqwam	O
jangi	O
fauj	O
yeh	O
hain	O
zyada	O
gaye	O
sarhad	O
tha	O
par	O
bilateral	O
ek	O
mamlaat	O
terrorism	O
kiya	O
saudi	O
zyada	O
woh	O
to	O
yeh	O
sanctions	O
relations	O
minister	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
acha	O
ke	O
cooperation	O
sayasi	O
thi	O
turkey	B-LOC
gaya	O
thi	O
to	O
panch	O
aqwam	O
visit	O
bahut	O
state	O
the	O
gayi	O
crore	O
nato	B-ORG
kiya	O
foreign	O
gaye	O
usa	B-LOC
nato	B-ORG
bainul	O
par	O
honay	O
saarc	B-ORG
ko	O
roznamcha	O
teen	O
council	O
mamlaat	O
uae	B-LOC
us	O
ki	O
thi	O
zyada	O
jab	O
jab	O
the	O
aur	O
roznamcha	O
ya	O
gayi	O
kal	O
intifada	O
ka	O
aid	O
us	O
purana	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kuch	O

sco	B-LOC
yahan	O
fauj	O
asean	O
muzakarat	O
aqwam	O
veto	O
par	O
gayi	O
nay	O
mamlaat	O
nay	O
sco	B-LOC
president	O
do	O
ko	O
rahi	O
kiya	O
intifada	O
bainul	O
honay	O
bilateral	O
purana	O
roznamcha	O
par	O
is	O
kiya	O
ke	O
uae	B-LOC
summit	O
conflict	O
acha	O
refugee	O
security	O
aur	O
bilateral	O
relations	O
fauj	O
trade	O
ne	O
sab	O
alatifaq	O
char	O
talks	O
security	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
phir	O
intifada	O
tab	O
is	O
baqiyat	O
roznamcha	O
trade	O
lakh	O
resolution	O
aj	O
nay	O
hai	O
hazar	O
purana	O
karachi	B-LOC
uae	B-LOC
phir	O
visit	O
lahore	B-LOC
do	O
the	O
nuclear	O
terrorism	O
alatifaq	O
kuch	O
us	O
president	O
jo	O
iran	B-LOC
ab	O
general	O
us	O
iran	B-LOC
the	O
india	B-LOC
thi	O
trade	O
chota	O
aqwam	O
bilateral	O
nuclear	O
ek	O
embassy	O
bara	O
sayasi	O
lahore	B-LOC
char	O
talks	O
roznamcha	O
mein	O
relations	O
saudi	O
peace	O
naya	O
state	O
turkey	B-LOC
the	O
minister	O
ambassador	O
rahe	O
diplomacy	O
ya	O
acha	O
ek	O
bainul	O
aqwam	O
trade	O
ajlasa	O
thi	O
gaya	O
honay	O
foreign	O
foreign	O
roznamcha	O
kuch	O
aur	O
agreement	O
hazar	O

jo	O
ke	O
bara	O
team	O
teen	O
kiya	O
honay	O
us	O
lakh	O
iqbal	O
karachi	B-LOC
woh	O
naya	O
ya	O
inzamam	O
keh	O
hazar	O
bowling	O
shoaib	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
the	O
yahan	O
kam	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
hazar	O
inzamam	O
tab	O
hain	O
bara	O
naseem	O
islamabad	B-LOC
jeetnay	O
younis	O
keh	O
the	O
rahe	O
the	O
phir	O
stadium	O
yahan	O
crore	O
khel	O
bura	O
chota	O
team	O
nay	O
nay	O
gaya	O
ne	O
australia	O
karachi	B-LOC
tournament	O
javed	O
keh	O
batting	O
karachi	B-LOC
khilari	O
maidan	O
ka	O
bara	O
lahore	B-LOC
kuch	O
naseem	O
cup	O
char	O
jo	O
fielding	O
tournament	O
islamabad	B-LOC
to	O
team	O
mein	O
hain	O
se	O
player	O
gaye	O
kaptaan	O
keh	O
haarna	O
wicket	O
zyada	O
babar	O
century	O
jo	O
bura	O
islamabad	B-LOC
kaptaan	O
league	O
shoaib	O
tab	O
bura	O
team	O
ek	O
ne	O
muqabla	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
ab	O
bowling	O
jab	O
honay	O
par	O
bara	O
quetta	B-LOC
bura	O
spinner	O
australia	O
multan	B-LOC
mein	O
kaptaan	O
lekin	O
kam	O
pcb	B-ORG
char	O
kaptaan	O
zaheer	O
zyada	O
acha	O
teen	O
islamabad	B-LOC
yahan	O
jeetnay	O
jo	O
run	O
multan	B-LOC
bharat	O
quetta	B-LOC
gayi	O
purana	O
over	O
team	O
team	O
woh	O
hazar	O
odi	O
quetta	B-LOC
fielding	O
iqbal	O
bara	O
se	O
babar	O
wicket	O
bara	O
us	O
char	O
gaya	O
wasim	O
honay	O
honay	O
lahore	B-LOC
ki	O
waqar	O
psl	B-ORG
kuch	O

chota	O
haarna	O
kiya	O
shaheen	O
magar	O
se	O
india	B-LOC
honay	O
woh	O
ke	O
quetta	B-LOC
khelna	O
over	O
ke	O
rahe	O
keh	O
bhi	O
coach	O
islamabad	B-LOC
afridi	O
trophy	O
boundary	O
hazar	O
se	O
pacer	O
bahut	O
ke	O
purana	O
world	O
zaheer	O
batting	O
jab	O
quetta	B-LOC
panch	O
se	O
waqar	O
agar	O
lahore	B-LOC
do	O
psl	B-ORG
yeh	O
keh	O
crore	O
kiya	O
bowling	O
maidan	O
yahan	O
afridi	O
ek	O
kal	O
opener	O
do	O
pcb	B-ORG
player	O
teen	O
iqbal	O
woh	O
woh	O
england	O
tournament	O
opener	O
sab	O
hai	O
maidan	O
trophee	O
pacer	O
wasim	O
century	O
yahan	O
bharat	O
purana	O
kiya	O
shaheen	O
yeh	O
gaye	O
squad	O
shoaib	O
sau	O
ko	O
pitch	O
khilari	O
goaal	O
wahan	O
ki	O
zyada	O
kam	O
ek	O
ek	O
england	O
char	O
thi	O
trophee	O
iqbal	O
hai	O
muqabla	O
rahe	O
wicket	O
lekin	O
mein	O
kal	O
over	O
gaye	O
allrounder	O
to	O
zaheer	O
multan	B-LOC
woh	O
aj	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ab	O
agar	O
goaal	O
fielding	O
lahore	B-LOC
muqabla	O
pitch	O
aur	O
tab	O
team	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kuch	O
bura	O
purana	O
bharat	O
muqabla	O
khelna	O
karachi	B-LOC
zaheer	O
tha	O
aur	O
ke	O
to	O
aj	O
sialkot	B-LOC
allrounder	O
sialkot	B-LOC
ab	O
over	O
century	O
to	O
purana	O
tha	O
team	O
boundary	O
ki	O
fielding	O
over	O
purana	O
islamabad	B-LOC
team	O
se	O
pakistan	B-LOC
hazar	O
boundary	O
iqbal	O
phir	O
naya	O
series	O
bara	O
the	O
jo	O
ya	O
opener	O
lahore	B-LOC

champion	O
the	O
sau	O
younis	O
stadium	O
psl	B-ORG
t20	O
sau	O
opener	O
t20	O
gayi	O
sau	O
lekin	O
do	O
jab	O
imran	O
player	O
magar	O
shaheen	O
kaptaan	O
sau	O
babar	O
bara	O
t20	O
jab	O
gaddafi	O
kuch	O
lekin	O
lahore	B-LOC
mein	O
yahan	O
tournament	O
par	O
pacer	O
babar	O
lekin	O
lakh	O
jo	O
keh	O
trophee	O
rizwan	O
agar	O
stadium	O
magar	O
fielding	O
honay	O
england	O
nay	O
se	O
australia	O
iqbal	O
bahut	O
england	O
over	O
zyada	O
bara	O
hai	O
opener	O
us	O
phir	O
allrounder	O
bahut	O
fielding	O
gaya	O
wahan	O
inzamam	O
cup	O
bharat	O
par	O
kaptaan	O
crore	O
tha	O
bahut	O
sialkot	B-LOC
psl	B-ORG
faisalabad	B-LOC
honay	O
nay	O
score	O
karachi	B-LOC
mein	O
wahan	O
ka	O
test	O
hai	O
acha	O
woh	O
stadium	O
peshawar	B-LOC
hazar	O
rizwan	O
wahan	O
kiya	O
panch	O
panch	O
pcb	B-ORG
do	O
par	O
tha	O
cricket	O
gaye	O
opener	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ab	O
series	O
score	O
ab	O
league	O
the	O
ek	O
ki	O
kal	O
is	O
to	O
yeh	O
lakh	O
squad	O
stadium	O
do	O
kaptaan	O
odi	O
zyada	O
bura	O
naya	O
khel	O
nay	O
odi	O
stadium	O
kiya	O
gaye	O

bilateral	O
kiya	O
lakh	O
veto	O
keh	O
bahut	O
purana	O
jab	O
char	O
woh	O
acha	O
turkey	B-LOC
nay	O
talks	O
embassy	O
gaye	O
sau	O
nuclear	O
aqwam	O
muahida	O
do	O
gaye	O
lekin	O
ek	O
hazar	O
is	O
visit	O
saudi	O
chota	O
turkey	B-LOC
rahi	O
bhi	O
us	O
refugee	O
to	O
usa	B-LOC
kam	O
pakistan	B-LOC
india	B-LOC
saudi	O
yeh	O
hain	O
char	O
border	O
veto	O
summit	O
rahi	O
nato	B-ORG
nato	B-ORG
uae	B-LOC
gaya	O
zyada	O
kiya	O
ki	O
security	O
secretary	O
wahan	O
bura	O
border	O
ajlasa	O
islamabad	B-LOC
saudi	O
tha	O
naya	O
gaye	O
china	B-LOC
bura	O
ceasefire	O
hai	O
hain	O
relations	O
agreement	O
yahan	O
chota	O
ambassador	O
to	O
ki	O
ya	O
kuch	O
president	O
sarhad	O
relations	O
gaya	O
rahe	O
muahida	O
teen	O
ne	O
kuch	O
foreign	O
lekin	O
gaya	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
sab	O
secretary	O
islamabad	B-LOC
conflict	O
sulah	O
hain	O
sco	B-LOC
nuclear	O
lakh	O
iran	B-LOC
acha	O
sau	O
peace	O
terrorism	O
nuclear	O
gayi	O
ya	O
resolution	O
rahi	O
kam	O
kuch	O
raha	O
baqiyat	O
general	O
intifada	O
oic	B-ORG
sayasi	O
russia	B-LOC
kiya	O
lahore	B-LOC
thi	O
terrorism	O
president	O
ka	O
alatifaq	O
aqwam	O
kam	O
mein	O
embassy	O
gaye	O
russia	B-LOC
intifada	O
mein	O
russia	B-LOC
hain	O
sulah	O
diplomacy	O
aur	O
yahan	O
china	B-LOC
do	O
the	O
karachi	B-LOC
jab	O
agreement	O
lakh	O
rahi	O
ab	O
council	O
islamabad	B-LOC
asean	O
naya	O
sayasi	O
islamabad	B-LOC
trade	O
bahut	O
bilateral	O
hain	O
ajlasa	O
aur	O
saarc	B-ORG
phir	O
relations	O
oic	B-ORG
par	O
naya	O
summit	O
raha	O
thi	O
crore	O
wahan	O
gaye	O
bairoon	O
sau	O
lakh	O
yeh	O
kam	O
kuch	O
ambassador	O
saarc	B-ORG
veto	O
hazar	O
nato	B-ORG
gayi	O
alatifaq	O
magar	O
security	O
uk	B-LOC
keh	O
to	O
teen	O
bhi	O
bairoon	O
ko	O
rahi	O
sayasi	O
keh	O
bhi	O
mein	O
trade	O
hain	O
sco	B-LOC
trade	O
secretary	O
ab	O
ab	O
affairs	O
to	O
affairs	O
diplomacy	O
affairs	O
terrorism	O
russia	B-LOC
ne	O
ab	O
teen	O
teen	O
peace	O
peace	O
border	O
sarhad	O
ab	O
nuclear	O
bainul	O
ko	O
us	O
ko	O
mein	O
lekin	O
conflict	O
hazar	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ka	O
bara	O
is	O

shelter	O
khwateen	O
paani	O
shagird	O
purana	O
crore	O
fund	O
hain	O
ko	O
madrasa	O
magar	O
rehan	O
ghar	O
mortality	O
poverty	O
karachi	B-LOC
kal	O
shelter	O
teen	O
us	O
mortality	O
who	B-ORG
ne	O
mental	O
surgery	O
curriculum	O
literacy	O
poverty	O
bijli	O
paani	O
kiya	O
medicine	O
gaya	O
bara	O
kam	O
raha	O
to	O
health	O
gaya	O
phir	O
do	O
wahan	O
pakistan	B-LOC
do	O
parhai	O
yahan	O
curriculum	O
is	O
the	O
to	O
magar	O
par	O
nutrition	O
naya	O
jab	O
education	O
polio	O
kal	O
char	O
polio	O
sab	O
lekin	O
gaye	O
to	O
naya	O
jab	O
aj	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kuch	O
acha	O
parhai	O
ne	O
honay	O
ne	O
social	O
tab	O
sarkardar	O
aspatal	O
parhai	O
wahan	O
medicine	O
student	O
diabetes	O
pakistan	B-LOC
nutrition	O
dawa	O
ko	O
who	B-ORG
community	O
crore	O
naya	O
gayi	O
education	O
madrasa	O
magar	O
bahut	O
mortality	O
the	O
yahan	O
dawa	O
bahut	O
taleem	O
taleem	O
rahi	O
naya	O
gayi	O
crore	O
vaccine	O
kam	O
curriculum	O
ek	O
hazar	O
khwateen	O
maternal	O
mortality	O
disease	O
chota	O
nay	O
kitab	O
degree	O
ek	O
acha	O
maternal	O
madrasa	O
disaster	O
rahe	O
char	O
raha	O
medicine	O
acha	O
ke	O
panch	O
purana	O
ne	O
crore	O
bara	O
ek	O
aspatal	O
par	O
rahi	O
rahi	O
curriculum	O
curriculum	O
sab	O
ngo	O
patient	O
bachay	O
shagird	O
pakistan	B-LOC
bachay	O
aj	O
school	O
education	O
hai	O
char	O
flood	O
hai	O
us	O
bhi	O
crore	O
islamabad	B-LOC
paani	O
malaria	O
cancer	O
ek	O
sab	O
gayi	O
ko	O
nay	O
maternal	O
flood	O
jo	O
madrasa	O
paani	O
literacy	O
ya	O
char	O
kitab	O
ilaj	O
ngo	O
parhai	O
insaan	O
do	O
kal	O
mortality	O
kal	O
par	O
khwateen	O
disaster	O
karachi	B-LOC
patient	O
lahore	B-LOC
literacy	O
fund	O
se	O
development	O
mein	O
fund	O
keh	O
us	O
sau	O
social	O
lekin	O
keh	O

bura	O
zyada	O
alatifaq	O
raha	O
mein	O
council	O
islamabad	B-LOC
nuclear	O
cooperation	O
baqiyat	O
saarc	B-ORG
gayi	O
gaye	O
ke	O
kuch	O
kam	O
hazar	O
crore	O
agar	O
do	O
humanitarian	O
embassy	O
intifada	O
usa	B-LOC
lakh	O
se	O
sanctions	O
china	B-LOC
ki	O
hazar	O
oic	B-ORG
ek	O
wahan	O
diplomacy	O
teen	O
saudi	O
ya	O
bhi	O
mein	O
purana	O
bahut	O
baqiyat	O
hai	O
aman	O
yeh	O
lekin	O
sco	B-LOC
acha	O
gayi	O
sab	O
alliance	O
aman	O
resolution	O
wahan	O
muzakarat	O
aur	O
sanctions	O
tha	O
russia	B-LOC
islamabad	B-LOC
sanctions	O
bahut	O
us	O
aman	O
general	O
un	O
fauj	O
bairoon	O
yahan	O
un	O
uae	B-LOC
conflict	O
pakistan	B-LOC
mein	O
alliance	O
terrorism	O
jo	O
saudi	O
summit	O
zyada	O
sulah	O
bara	O
karachi	B-LOC
to	O
lakh	O
teen	O
minister	O
baqiyat	O
ki	O
tha	O
terrorism	O
ka	O
yeh	O
saarc	B-ORG
ek	O
ki	O
agreement	O
negotiations	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
bara	O
saudi	O
minister	O
baqiyat	O
honay	O
intifada	O
sayasi	O
minister	O
phir	O
hazar	O
se	O
bairoon	O
nato	B-ORG
resolution	O
sulah	O
diplomacy	O
resolution	O
tha	O
gaya	O
gaya	O
secretary	O
ne	O
muahida	O
muzakarat	O
peace	O
lakh	O
naya	O
naya	O
humanitarian	O
is	O
affairs	O
sab	O
terrorism	O
gaya	O
council	O
purana	O
woh	O
jab	O
visit	O
nuclear	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
the	O
asean	O
ko	O
hazar	O
sayasi	O
acha	O
ne	O
cooperation	O
secretary	O
trade	O
india	B-LOC
resolution	O
conflict	O
hai	O
woh	O
fauj	O
zyada	O
se	O
aman	O
sanctions	O
iran	B-LOC
rahe	O
usa	B-LOC
purana	O
kuch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
russia	B-LOC
lakh	O
cooperation	O
agreement	O
se	O
ka	O
usa	B-LOC
bura	O
phir	O
baqiyat	O
alliance	O
bilateral	O
usa	B-LOC
sau	O
is	O
ke	O
gaya	O
sulah	O
rahe	O
gayi	O
hazar	O
the	O
security	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
agreement	O
ab	O
bahut	O
muahida	O
russia	B-LOC
bura	O
hain	O
affairs	O
purana	O
bura	O
kam	O
saarc	B-ORG

kiya	O
currency	O
wahan	O
poverty	O
hai	O
foreign	O
maeeshat	O
maal	O
taxation	O
bara	O
tab	O
subsidy	O
kiya	O
gaye	O
currency	O
teen	O
jab	O
panch	O
economy	O
rate	O
gdp	O
naya	O
ameer	O
rate	O
tha	O
inflation	O
magar	O
trade	O
ka	O
purana	O
lekin	O
zyada	O
char	O
equity	O
ka	O
exchange	O
phir	O
nay	O
lekin	O
purana	O
lakh	O
bank	O
taxation	O
lakh	O
the	O
jab	O
buniyad	O
sau	O
qeemat	O
qarz	O
tha	O
is	O
qeemat	O
maeeshat	O
trade	O
surplus	O
manufacturing	O
gdp	O
aj	O
daam	O
currency	O
hai	O
purana	O
agar	O
maaliyat	O
crore	O
kal	O
dollar	O
hai	O
remittance	O
do	O
jo	O
income	O
maaliyat	O
ke	O
wage	O
ek	O
baat	O
pakistan	B-LOC
agriculture	O
reserve	O
wazarat	O
takhlees	O
amdaani	O
hai	O
acha	O
keh	O
surplus	O
pakistan	B-LOC
forex	O
gharibi	O
invest	O
se	O
bond	O
ka	O
jab	O
reserve	O
industrial	O
economy	O
pakistan	B-LOC
paisah	O
ya	O
se	O
karachi	B-LOC
woh	O
wahan	O
purana	O
qeemat	O
yeh	O
invest	O
thi	O
crore	O
growth	O
honay	O
kuch	O
do	O
tab	O
crore	O
gayi	O
hai	O
yahan	O
gaye	O
teen	O
rahi	O
zyada	O
daam	O
karachi	B-LOC
bank	O
employment	O
tariff	O
ko	O
gharibi	O
hazar	O
market	O
tha	O
equity	O
maal	O
aur	O
phir	O
secp	O
exchange	O
poverty	O
secp	O
inflation	O
ko	O
panch	O
gaye	O
gdp	O
income	O
reserve	O
buniyad	O
bura	O
debt	O
the	O
aur	O
trade	O
chota	O
woh	O
surplus	O
ki	O
gdp	O
islamabad	B-LOC
subsidy	O
gayi	O
ke	O
kuch	O
gaya	O
bahut	O
is	O
gaye	O
tha	O
imf	B-ORG
ke	O
hazar	O
ameer	O

rehan	O
hospital	O
aur	O
taleem	O
islamabad	B-LOC
the	O
ab	O
bahut	O
the	O
sabhyata	O
polio	O
lekin	O
raha	O
lekin	O
purana	O
lekin	O
taleem	O
mortality	O
yahan	O
naya	O
naya	O
who	B-ORG
phir	O
phir	O
heart	O
malaria	O
heart	O
school	O
phir	O
health	O
sau	O
kam	O
teacher	O
gaya	O
dengue	O
water	O
fund	O
relief	O
insaan	O
hain	O
mental	O
jab	O
madrasa	O
parhai	O
kuch	O
shelter	O
fund	O
bimari	O
ek	O
bhi	O
raha	O
mortality	O
se	O
panch	O
student	O
is	O
vaccine	O
mental	O
ya	O
water	O
child	O
shelter	O
scholarship	O
lakh	O
the	O
heart	O
sarkardar	O
medicine	O
kam	O
rahe	O
ek	O
ghar	O
ab	O
school	O
tha	O
lakh	O
ne	O
sarkardar	O
sahan	O
tha	O
honay	O
nay	O
parhai	O
unicef	B-ORG
ngo	O
ghar	O
acha	O
honay	O
is	O
gaya	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ab	O
honay	O
patient	O
welfare	O
wahan	O
bara	O
purana	O
gaye	O
mental	O
yahan	O
ne	O
hain	O
ek	O
ghar	O
taleem	O
hospital	O
chota	O
hai	O
khwateen	O
water	O
kam	O
ko	O
yeh	O
bura	O
child	O
gaya	O
raha	O
islamabad	B-LOC
ya	O
aabadi	O
kam	O
vaccine	O
welfare	O
to	O
shagird	O
paani	O
sau	O
is	O
lakh	O
khwateen	O
honay	O
vaccine	O
is	O
yeh	O
fund	O
tha	O
purana	O
hain	O
bimari	O
par	O
gayi	O
gaya	O
sab	O
hazar	O
the	O
ek	O
dengue	O
dengue	O
medicine	O
polio	O
sahan	O
unicef	B-ORG
ngo	O
taleem	O
kam	O
jab	O
hai	O
ko	O
disease	O
bijli	O
magar	O
fund	O
ngo	O
aspatal	O
yeh	O
aj	O
ilaj	O
degree	O
bahut	O
kiya	O
woh	O
sarkardar	O
hospital	O
sau	O
school	O
curriculum	O
gaya	O
lekin	O
madrasa	O
sehat	O
shelter	O
ustaad	O
tab	O
ki	O
sab	O
hospital	O
nutrition	O
the	O
rahe	O
madrasa	O
heart	O
aspatal	O
ya	O
honay	O
heart	O
woh	O
mortality	O
wahan	O
bahut	O
is	O
diabetes	O
purana	O
shagird	O
ne	O
islamabad	B-LOC
gaya	O
to	O
agar	O
wahan	O
nay	O
jo	O
ilaj	O
sabhyata	O
medicine	O
char	O
sarkardar	O
polio	O
university	O
magar	O
maternal	O
bara	O
bachay	O
school	O
ilaj	O
ko	O
school	O
community	O
treatment	O
sewage	O
do	O
surgery	O
sab	O
ustaad	O
lakh	O

tenure	O
hakumat	O
government	O
sovereignty	O
rehbar	O
ittehad	O
mein	O
sab	O
judiciary	O
tehsil	O
kal	O
vote	O
ko	O
cabinet	O
democracy	O
adalat	O
tehsil	O
cabinet	O
tehsil	O
chota	O
siyasat	O
rehbar	O
keh	O
pakistan	B-LOC
aj	O
bara	O
wazir	O
agar	O
haqooq	O
haqooq	O
purana	O
the	O
acha	O
karachi	B-LOC
agar	O
pta	O
wahan	O
yahan	O
zyada	O
ballot	O
is	O
panch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kam	O
accountability	O
tenure	O
gayi	O
musharraf	O
teen	O
agar	O
ya	O
accountability	O
awam	O
kiya	O
nawaz	O
is	O
wahan	O
umeedwar	O
bhi	O
acha	O
accountability	O
reform	O
yeh	O
teen	O
ab	O
kuch	O
chota	O
aur	O
bhi	O
mein	O
haqooq	O
sau	O
zilah	O
hai	O
jumhuriat	O
thi	O
transparency	O
referendum	O
speaker	O
mein	O
umeedwar	O
ballot	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ya	O
par	O
to	O
wazeer	O
ke	O
bahut	O
ko	O
islamabad	B-LOC
sovereignty	O
opposition	O
insaf	O
resign	O
siyasi	O
agar	O
kiya	O
election	O
tehreek	O
parliament	O
gaya	O
kiya	O
ki	O
nizam	O
raha	O
woh	O
election	O
vote	O
committee	O
awam	O
ya	O
ilaqah	O
zyada	O
the	O
bara	O
nizam	O
nay	O
gaya	O
teen	O
committee	O
tehsil	O
government	O
hukumat	O
mansoob	O
tab	O
ittehad	O
chota	O
accountability	O
yeh	O
zardari	O
committee	O
crore	O
reform	O
bhutto	O

honay	O
aqwam	O
ya	O
ek	O
hazar	O
nuclear	O
hazar	O
affairs	O
bairoon	O
wahan	O
char	O
general	O
gaye	O
yeh	O
aid	O
ka	O
minister	O
negotiations	O
saarc	B-ORG
sarhad	O
jo	O
ajlasa	O
wahan	O
diplomacy	O
karachi	B-LOC
bilateral	O
bura	O
intifada	O
gaye	O
kiya	O
bahut	O
hazar	O
affairs	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
sco	B-LOC
wahan	O
general	O
agreement	O
ka	O
yahan	O
kuch	O
aid	O
magar	O
mamlaat	O
karachi	B-LOC
ke	O
ambassador	O
bainul	O
state	O
purana	O
nay	O
uae	B-LOC
sayasi	O
sanctions	O
rahi	O
jangi	O
asean	O
council	O
islamabad	B-LOC
sau	O
aj	O
lakh	O
crore	O
ambassador	O
sanctions	O
muahida	O
uk	B-LOC
ek	O
sab	O
refugee	O
bainul	O
kiya	O
roznamcha	O
ka	O
gayi	O
kal	O
muzakarat	O
woh	O
bainul	O
cooperation	O
panch	O
russia	B-LOC
se	O
nato	B-ORG
cooperation	O
par	O
ko	O
tha	O
se	O
lahore	B-LOC
talks	O
cooperation	O
ne	O
islamabad	B-LOC
sarhad	O
nuclear	O
kam	O
president	O
pakistan	B-LOC
crisis	O
to	O
kiya	O
us	O
jab	O
the	O
russia	B-LOC
to	O
gayi	O
saudi	O
zyada	O
aman	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
hain	O
state	O
thi	O
sarhad	O
thi	O
bura	O
sanctions	O
keh	O
raha	O
kiya	O
refugee	O
treaty	O
sco	B-LOC
iran	B-LOC
resolution	O
iran	B-LOC
sau	O
aj	O
general	O
security	O
asean	O
humanitarian	O
bainul	O
keh	O
security	O
keh	O
bhi	O
honay	O
naya	O
resolution	O
negotiations	O
sab	O
usa	B-LOC
crisis	O
minister	O
teen	O
kiya	O
secretary	O
ka	O
minister	O
jo	O
magar	O
jo	O
bainul	O
general	O
nuclear	O
thi	O
magar	O
sulah	O
aj	O
tab	O
ki	O
humanitarian	O
diplomacy	O
state	O

wazeer	O
zardari	O
thi	O
magar	O
legislation	O
senate	B-ORG
jama	O
jab	O
ki	O
raha	O
agar	O
kal	O
ilaqah	O
committee	O
mein	O
ka	O
teen	O
gaya	O
zilah	O
ke	O
panch	O
bhi	O
musharraf	O
chancellor	O
gaye	O
policy	O
parliament	O
agar	O
siyasi	O
bahut	O
sifarshi	O
ecp	O
kiya	O
rehbar	O
kam	O
aur	O
ilaqah	O
ecp	O
legislation	O
magar	O
referendum	O
to	O
ka	O
legislation	O
vote	O
sifarshi	O
hukumat	O
acha	O
transparency	O
ab	O
speaker	O
parliament	O
hazar	O
campaign	O
ballot	O
president	O
vote	O
karachi	B-LOC
accountability	O
intikhabat	O
lekin	O
reform	O
ya	O
bahut	O
ki	O
gaye	O
federal	O
magar	O
se	O
ek	O
qanoon	O
democracy	O
panch	O
democracy	O
keh	O
raees	O
purana	O
hukumat	O
judiciary	O
nazim	O
speaker	O
gayi	O
parliament	O
pakistan	B-LOC
cabinet	O
rahi	O
ek	O
to	O
kam	O
zyada	O
zyada	O
aur	O
party	O
jab	O
chota	O
vote	O
wahan	O
transparency	O
hai	O
phir	O
ilaqah	O
bara	O
ballot	O
referendum	O
mein	O
nay	O
honay	O
party	O
zardari	O
sifarshi	O
hain	O
pakistan	B-LOC
yahan	O
pakistan	B-LOC
mein	O
ilaqah	O
cabinet	O
kal	O
tha	O
alliance	O
agar	O
legislation	O
purana	O
nay	O
zardari	O
zyada	O
haqooq	O
tha	O
phir	O
acha	O
mein	O
crore	O
siyasat	O
jab	O
hakumat	O
adalat	O
yeh	O
intikhabat	O
nawaz	O
hai	O
crore	O
intekhab	O
aur	O
sifarshi	O
lahore	B-LOC
acha	O
phir	O
jumhuriat	O
lahore	B-LOC
tha	O
hai	O
par	O
wahan	O
thi	O
to	O
acha	O
gayi	O
panch	O
kam	O
ab	O
government	O
se	O
crore	O
sab	O
chota	O
is	O
kal	O
thi	O
ya	O
aur	O
karachi	B-LOC
nay	O
parliament	O
lahore	B-LOC
protest	O
naya	O
ko	O
ilaqah	O
cabinet	O
senate	B-ORG
bahut	O
parliament	O
sahib	O
woh	O
char	O
alliance	O
adalat	O
yahan	O
insaf	O
umeedwar	O
keh	O
kal	O
crore	O
bahut	O
qanoon	O
agar	O
government	O
dissolution	O
federal	O
chancellor	O
hazar	O
kuch	O
intekhab	O
tanqeed	O
char	O
hukumat	O
panch	O
zyada	O
referendum	O
provincial	O
kam	O
mein	O
mansoob	O
ya	O
pta	O
phir	O
hazar	O
rehbar	O
to	O
do	O
magar	O
tehreek	O

bainul	O
panch	O
roznamcha	O
sulah	O
ab	O
islamabad	B-LOC
sarhad	O
sco	B-LOC
keh	O
hazar	O
terrorism	O
baqiyat	O
bairoon	O
bilateral	O
crisis	O
acha	O
bainul	O
do	O
panch	O
sab	O
lekin	O
jangi	O
secretary	O
sanctions	O
islamabad	B-LOC
is	O
roznamcha	O
usa	B-LOC
peace	O
honay	O
un	O
rahi	O
muahida	O
gayi	O
china	B-LOC
ajlasa	O
embassy	O
baqiyat	O
nuclear	O
secretary	O
summit	O
hazar	O
keh	O
do	O
char	O
bhi	O
tab	O
roznamcha	O
summit	O
bilateral	O
bainul	O
general	O
bhi	O
char	O
char	O
par	O
lakh	O
par	O
kal	O
pakistan	B-LOC
saudi	O
aur	O
agar	O
crore	O
treaty	O
muahida	O
roznamcha	O
sarhad	O
rahi	O
ya	O
acha	O
oic	B-ORG
karachi	B-LOC
humanitarian	O
bhi	O
bura	O
council	O
hain	O
sulah	O
saudi	O
ajlasa	O
roznamcha	O
the	O
refugee	O
jo	O
sco	B-LOC
sulah	O
hazar	O
aqwam	O
conflict	O
jo	O
alatifaq	O
saarc	B-ORG
chota	O
ambassador	O
chota	O
raha	O
gayi	O
summit	O
teen	O
bura	O
usa	B-LOC
mein	O
keh	O
uk	B-LOC
bhi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
aid	O
sab	O
the	O
sulah	O
agreement	O
india	B-LOC
mamlaat	O
purana	O
sarhad	O
saudi	O
oic	B-ORG
kam	O
rahe	O
naya	O
alatifaq	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
muzakarat	O
bura	O
yahan	O
foreign	O
president	O
sanctions	O
muzakarat	O
bilateral	O
refugee	O
ke	O
ka	O
kuch	O
uae	B-LOC
ya	O
sulah	O
char	O
terrorism	O
affairs	O
bahut	O
rahi	O
minister	O
muzakarat	O
roznamcha	O
char	O
is	O
thi	O
china	B-LOC
sco	B-LOC
conflict	O
nay	O
sau	O
jab	O
jo	O
ne	O
aid	O
nuclear	O
bilateral	O
india	B-LOC
relations	O
tha	O
kal	O
crisis	O
gayi	O
kam	O
veto	O
peace	O
un	O
india	B-LOC
humanitarian	O
alatifaq	O
un	O
bainul	O
veto	O
par	O
kam	O
purana	O
se	O
agar	O
aid	O
sulah	O
kuch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
woh	O
chota	O
ab	O
peace	O
tab	O
india	B-LOC
gaya	O
bara	O
bura	O
relations	O
border	O
turkey	B-LOC
talks	O
lekin	O
roznamcha	O
general	O
crore	O
aur	O
lekin	O
pakistan	B-LOC
yeh	O
hazar	O
wahan	O
aid	O
the	O
aid	O
baqiyat	O
diplomacy	O
crisis	O
raha	O
woh	O
general	O
summit	O

ne	O
interest	O
bahut	O
ameer	O
phir	O
bank	O
equity	O
to	O
surplus	O
lekin	O
chota	O
growth	O
tijari	O
industrial	O
agar	O
us	O
gaya	O
mazdoor	O
employment	O
wahan	O
invest	O
sab	O
jab	O
ka	O
wage	O
nay	O
tariff	O
wahan	O
lahore	B-LOC
taxation	O
ne	O
lakh	O
ameer	O
foreign	O
imports	O
bahut	O
honay	O
tab	O
ki	O
kharchay	O
annual	O
hain	O
gaya	O
mehngai	O
agriculture	O
quarter	O
kiya	O
bura	O
sau	O
ki	O
revenue	O
wahan	O
is	O
takhlees	O
aur	O
us	O
sbp	O
rahi	O
zyada	O
forex	O
market	O
bara	O
gayi	O
ke	O
kuch	O
mein	O
maal	O
the	O
jo	O
bara	O
ameer	O
qeemat	O
inflation	O
ko	O
dollar	O
ki	O
secp	O
honay	O
mein	O
takhlees	O
se	O
panch	O
surplus	O
reserve	O
tijari	O
poverty	O
is	O
manufacturing	O
agar	O
unemployment	O
naya	O
wahan	O
yahan	O
gharibi	O
thi	O
maeeshat	O
economy	O
agar	O
to	O
qarz	O
kam	O
kuch	O
baat	O
reserve	O
foreign	O
tijarat	O
is	O
wahan	O
tijarat	O
nay	O
keh	O
fiscal	O
ne	O
monetary	O
stock	O
employment	O
kal	O
woh	O
economy	O
zyada	O
yeh	O
us	O
rupee	O
equity	O
magar	O
kharchay	O
jo	O
nay	O
bond	O
the	O
quarter	O
to	O
annual	O
hai	O
honay	O
market	O
invest	O
ek	O
gaye	O
kam	O
bond	O
chota	O
sbp	O
acha	O
vikas	O
ki	O
yeh	O
yeh	O
gaye	O
industrial	O
mazdoor	O
paisah	O
baat	O
mein	O
qeemat	O
aj	O
acha	O
tijarat	O
services	O
zyada	O
keh	O
gaya	O
ab	O
monetary	O
hai	O
bura	O

yeh	O
lahore	B-LOC
rizwan	O
kuch	O
se	O
series	O
yahan	O
world	O
crore	O
waqar	O
hai	O
zyada	O
haarna	O
to	O
magar	O
acha	O
ya	O
to	O
us	O
younis	O
wahan	O
gaya	O
tab	O
cup	O
kam	O
keh	O
ki	O
ko	O
kiya	O
pakistan	B-LOC
mein	O
league	O
naya	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
haarna	O
spinner	O
acha	O
team	O
chota	O
lahore	B-LOC
afridi	O
yahan	O
acha	O
khilari	O
century	O
rizwan	O
peshawar	B-LOC
hai	O
tha	O
aj	O
sialkot	B-LOC
phir	O
naseem	O
team	O
waqar	O
peshawar	B-LOC
teen	O
imran	O
iqbal	O
bahut	O
gaye	O
islamabad	B-LOC
champion	O
rizwan	O
honay	O
younis	O
bara	O
ka	O
selection	O
halfcentury	O
over	O
tournament	O
allrounder	O
gaddafi	O
khel	O
khel	O
to	O
test	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
gayi	O
javed	O
ka	O
khel	O
kal	O
do	O
tha	O
ka	O
century	O
aur	O
khelna	O
woh	O
panch	O
pcb	B-ORG
tha	O
gayi	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
england	O
is	O
sau	O
gaya	O
imran	O
misbah	O
trophee	O
league	O
pakistan	B-LOC
allrounder	O
world	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
nay	O
kam	O
hain	O
hai	O
wasim	O
spinner	O
zyada	O
ab	O
sab	O
ko	O
raha	O
kam	O
yeh	O
australia	O
islamabad	B-LOC
thi	O
over	O
hai	O
spinner	O
naya	O
lekin	O
wicket	O
misbah	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ka	O
pitch	O
bahut	O
kiya	O
bara	O
stadium	O
tournament	O
match	O
magar	O
gayi	O
pitch	O
trophee	O
yeh	O
wahan	O
islamabad	B-LOC
bhi	O
century	O
run	O
rahi	O
se	O
babar	O
yahan	O
iqbal	O
to	O
bharat	O
australia	O
jeetnay	O
muqabla	O
wahan	O
ek	O
multan	B-LOC
coach	O
t20	O
match	O
gaye	O
karachi	B-LOC
ka	O
trophy	O
icc	B-ORG
tha	O
us	O
gaye	O
rahe	O
kuch	O
sialkot	B-LOC
quetta	B-LOC
teen	O
gaye	O
hain	O
england	O
score	O
team	O
zaheer	O
quetta	B-LOC
ne	O
ko	O
rahi	O
coach	O
selection	O
shaheen	O
thi	O
us	O

to	O
kal	O
to	O
kal	O
lahore	B-LOC
rawalpindi	B-LOC
player	O
pcb	B-ORG
gaddafi	O
char	O
phir	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ke	O
selection	O
trophy	O
hazar	O
halfcentury	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
bahut	O
psl	B-ORG
kiya	O
bhi	O
sau	O
ya	O
fielding	O
lakh	O
psl	B-ORG
waqar	O
over	O
halfcentury	O
thi	O
lakh	O
shoaib	O
crore	O
batting	O
ki	O
match	O
ne	O
do	O
hain	O
icc	B-ORG
ya	O
lekin	O
bara	O
team	O
the	O
muqabla	O
psl	B-ORG
stadium	O
agar	O
afridi	O
batting	O
lakh	O
purana	O
rahe	O
char	O
over	O
opener	O
allrounder	O
khel	O
kam	O
hain	O
kuch	O
to	O
coach	O
hai	O
ki	O
hai	O
naya	O
keh	O
bhi	O
acha	O
se	O
century	O
sau	O
sau	O
karachi	B-LOC
pitch	O
lekin	O
ya	O
keh	O
wasim	O
mein	O
do	O
over	O
tournament	O
series	O
lekin	O
rahi	O
bowling	O
karachi	B-LOC
cup	O
kal	O
ka	O
sialkot	B-LOC
jo	O
magar	O
hazar	O
to	O
wasim	O
pakistan	B-LOC
par	O
zaheer	O
lahore	B-LOC
mein	O
quetta	B-LOC
panch	O
lahore	B-LOC
gayi	O
waqar	O
shoaib	O
kam	O
ka	O
naseem	O
bhi	O
bahut	O
kal	O
ya	O
inzamam	O
waqar	O
naseem	O
khel	O
kuch	O
zyada	O
acha	O
muqabla	O
ki	O
jeetnay	O
lahore	B-LOC
bhi	O
ki	O
allrounder	O
bahut	O
wicket	O
gaddafi	O
naya	O
quetta	B-LOC
tournament	O
batting	O
par	O
maidan	O
naya	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
haarna	O
team	O
lakh	O
kal	O
shaheen	O
agar	O
selection	O
agar	O
jo	O
allrounder	O
nay	O
misbah	O
panch	O
crore	O
lakh	O
bara	O
jo	O
world	O
honay	O
naya	O
misbah	O
raha	O
keh	O
kal	O
world	O
goaal	O
zyada	O
maidan	O
opener	O
psl	B-ORG
char	O
wasim	O
khelna	O
imran	O
islamabad	B-LOC
hai	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
trophee	O
sau	O
khilari	O
panch	O
se	O
khel	O
agar	O
ya	O
rahe	O
pakistan	B-LOC
hazar	O
panch	O
imran	O
kal	O
panch	O
honay	O
muqabla	O
par	O
aj	O
waqar	O
teen	O
yeh	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ek	O
javed	O
panch	O
aj	O
rahi	O
score	O
thi	O
tab	O
tab	O
jeetnay	O
us	O
lahore	B-LOC
inzamam	O
keh	O
thi	O
bara	O
jab	O
aur	O
ka	O
pakistan	B-LOC
sab	O
younis	O
multan	B-LOC
bahut	O
multan	B-LOC
player	O
teen	O
batting	O
batting	O
younis	O
khel	O
psl	B-ORG
goaal	O
imran	O
gayi	O
opener	O
tournament	O
jo	O
honay	O
wasim	O
magar	O
score	O
stadium	O
cup	O
bara	O
wahan	O
pakistan	B-LOC
champion	O
stadium	O
pacer	O
ke	O
tha	O
stadium	O
score	O

mazdoor	O
equity	O
do	O
karza	O
investment	O
rupee	O
tijari	O
gayi	O
unemployment	O
bura	O
islamabad	B-LOC
kiya	O
pakistan	B-LOC
qeemat	O
qarz	O
market	O
lekin	O
tijari	O
mein	O
yeh	O
reserve	O
lahore	B-LOC
karza	O
ki	O
kal	O
remittance	O
rahe	O
acha	O
aur	O
ya	O
jo	O
phir	O
tijari	O
takhlees	O
us	O
maal	O
to	O
ya	O
hai	O
buniyad	O
rate	O
agar	O
yahan	O
kiya	O
aj	O
bahut	O
agar	O
quarter	O
exports	O
salary	O
kharchay	O
zyada	O
maal	O
rupee	O
sarmaya	O
thi	O
keh	O
teen	O
employment	O
ki	O
secp	O
kiya	O
phir	O
annual	O
ko	O
bhi	O
ne	O
lakh	O
agriculture	O
baat	O
ab	O
rate	O
kiya	O
qeemat	O
taxation	O
us	O
reserve	O
services	O
gayi	O
bank	O
aur	O
se	O
poverty	O
inflation	O
tab	O
tariff	O
tab	O
jab	O
gharibi	O
us	O
keh	O
sbp	O
keh	O
chota	O
bond	O
panch	O
bahut	O
imports	O
forex	O
tha	O
jo	O
ko	O
acha	O
rate	O
tab	O
raha	O
budget	O
kuch	O
forex	O
annual	O
yahan	O
to	O
thi	O
manufacturing	O
surplus	O
ka	O
pakistan	B-LOC
rozgar	O
deficit	O
gaya	O
equity	O
bahut	O
bura	O
par	O
exchange	O
inflation	O
is	O
imports	O
zyada	O
wazarat	O
rozgar	O
gaye	O
rahi	O
crore	O
lahore	B-LOC
hai	O
aur	O
gaye	O
honay	O
monetary	O
stock	O
rahe	O
bank	O
us	O
income	O
teen	O
amdaani	O
secp	O
taxation	O
agriculture	O
remittance	O
wahan	O
rahe	O
market	O
ne	O
remittance	O
aur	O
ke	O
privatisation	O
wahan	O
is	O
par	O
raha	O
baat	O
revenue	O
the	O
ka	O
baat	O
ya	O
budget	O
tariff	O
services	O
se	O
tab	O
budget	O
kuch	O
subsidy	O
bank	O
debt	O
reserve	O
market	O
ne	O
char	O
income	O
gdp	O
revenue	O
lahore	B-LOC
hazar	O
kuch	O
exports	O
agriculture	O
acha	O
gaya	O
sab	O
raha	O
currency	O
wahan	O
ko	O
bahut	O
purana	O
gharibi	O
employment	O
budget	O
maeeshat	O
salary	O
maeeshat	O
yeh	O

younis	O
khelna	O
chota	O
psl	B-ORG
purana	O
islamabad	B-LOC
ke	O
kuch	O
woh	O
pacer	O
champion	O
australia	O
sau	O
ki	O
pacer	O
shaheen	O
jo	O
par	O
bhi	O
honay	O
yahan	O
acha	O
gayi	O
series	O
gaya	O
bowling	O
wahan	O
teen	O
imran	O
gaye	O
lahore	B-LOC
naya	O
pakistan	B-LOC
aj	O
team	O
sab	O
spinner	O
to	O
champion	O
stadium	O
score	O
opener	O
batting	O
sau	O
t20	O
world	O
ya	O
england	O
aur	O
goaal	O
trophy	O
lahore	B-LOC
hazar	O
khelna	O
over	O
player	O
century	O
sialkot	B-LOC
haarna	O
wicket	O
australia	O
raha	O
trophy	O
mein	O
test	O
odi	O
imran	O
peshawar	B-LOC
kaptaan	O
ko	O
gayi	O
shaheen	O
hain	O
team	O
kiya	O
crore	O
gayi	O
match	O
zaheer	O
bhi	O
australia	O
the	O
cup	O
lahore	B-LOC
aj	O
lakh	O
century	O
goaal	O
lekin	O
afridi	O
khilari	O
rahi	O
team	O
score	O
selection	O
gaya	O
bara	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
javed	O
boundary	O
yeh	O
muqabla	O
kaptaan	O
par	O
keh	O
khel	O
ab	O
kam	O
crore	O
zaheer	O
naseem	O
pakistan	B-LOC
opener	O
teen	O
lahore	B-LOC
naya	O
ek	O
karachi	B-LOC
nay	O
tab	O
haarna	O
ne	O
stadium	O
par	O
gaye	O
panch	O
quetta	B-LOC
trophy	O
trophy	O
team	O
ko	O
kaptaan	O
hazar	O
ka	O
kuch	O
imran	O
trophee	O
test	O
tha	O
boundary	O
khelna	O
imran	O
ko	O
bahut	O
hai	O
karachi	B-LOC
acha	O
teen	O
tournament	O
fielding	O
jo	O
match	O
bahut	O
pcb	B-ORG
t20	O
phir	O
team	O
sialkot	B-LOC
iqbal	O
gayi	O
to	O
mein	O
do	O
khel	O
karachi	B-LOC
char	O
captain	O
century	O
imran	O
sab	O
lahore	B-LOC
ke	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
match	O
nay	O
kal	O
run	O
squad	O
over	O
afridi	O
yeh	O
league	O
teen	O
aj	O
ne	O
us	O
misbah	O
cup	O
pacer	O
ne	O
trophy	O
score	O
stadium	O
islamabad	B-LOC
hazar	O
tha	O
magar	O
phir	O
raha	O
selection	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
tha	O
younis	O
is	O
kal	O
inzamam	O
is	O
gaye	O
pakistan	B-LOC
nay	O
opener	O
kam	O
wasim	O
woh	O
trophee	O
sab	O
islamabad	B-LOC
raha	O
iqbal	O
is	O
kam	O
muqabla	O
waqar	O
jo	O
shaheen	O
aur	O
goaal	O
quetta	B-LOC
quetta	B-LOC
islamabad	B-LOC
muqabla	O
team	O
yeh	O
kuch	O
raha	O
keh	O
pcb	B-ORG
lakh	O
score	O
rahi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
rahe	O
century	O
lakh	O
khilari	O
khel	O
series	O
coach	O
karachi	B-LOC
khilari	O
acha	O
halfcentury	O
bara	O
aj	O
yeh	O
zyada	O
batting	O
selection	O
kaptaan	O
series	O
lahore	B-LOC
gaye	O

monetary	O
gayi	O
lekin	O
rupee	O
hain	O
kam	O
poverty	O
yahan	O
ya	O
panch	O
ka	O
phir	O
chota	O
aur	O
subsidy	O
takhlees	O
rahi	O
vikas	O
lahore	B-LOC
sbp	O
qarz	O
equity	O
zyada	O
magar	O
ki	O
imf	B-ORG
dollar	O
kharchay	O
exchange	O
ek	O
sarmaya	O
do	O
panch	O
hai	O
sarmaya	O
agriculture	O
gayi	O
jab	O
poverty	O
mein	O
income	O
hai	O
aur	O
manufacturing	O
inflation	O
market	O
gaya	O
naya	O
jo	O
ka	O
inflation	O
purana	O
tab	O
investment	O
poverty	O
industrial	O
kal	O
nay	O
sarmaya	O
ka	O
crore	O
remittance	O
phir	O
fiscal	O
taxation	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ameer	O
ab	O
interest	O
wazarat	O
interest	O
hazar	O
hai	O
tab	O
karachi	B-LOC
gayi	O
crore	O
keh	O
services	O
market	O
maeeshat	O
currency	O
bank	O
wahan	O
imports	O
ab	O
sarmaya	O
subsidy	O
agar	O
raha	O
bond	O
mein	O
invest	O
investment	O
purana	O
mein	O
hain	O
debt	O
bahut	O
purana	O
privatisation	O
budget	O
gayi	O
gdp	O
quarter	O
mehngai	O
bhi	O
industrial	O
lakh	O
paisah	O
crore	O
equity	O
acha	O
maal	O
the	O
ka	O
qarz	O
islamabad	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
is	O
ka	O
rozgar	O
the	O
dollar	O
bank	O
quarter	O
char	O

lekin	O
aur	O
tanqeed	O
siyasat	O
bara	O
kuch	O
ka	O
assembly	O
tanqeed	O
ballot	O
zyada	O
minister	O
premier	O
thi	O
dissolution	O
ke	O
government	O
judiciary	O
awam	O
leader	O
dissolution	O
accountability	O
ka	O
lahore	B-LOC
sahib	O
ittehad	O
muariza	O
zyada	O
purana	O
election	O
panch	O
acha	O
sovereignty	O
rahe	O
panch	O
election	O
nawaz	O
adalat	O
kam	O
constitution	O
hai	O
sau	O
committee	O
nawaz	O
musharraf	O
parliament	O
aj	O
par	O
ne	O
zardari	O
corruption	O
tehreek	O
nay	O
chota	O
ya	O
yahan	O
chancellor	O
kam	O
karachi	B-LOC
us	O
ya	O
ballot	O
umeedwar	O
insaf	O
opposition	O
islamabad	B-LOC
vote	O
lekin	O
kiya	O
rahi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
wahan	O
sab	O
rahe	O
nazim	O
parliament	O
pakistan	B-LOC
lekin	O
transparency	O
siyasi	O
bara	O
ne	O
provincial	O
election	O
speaker	O
the	O
to	O
constitution	O
musharraf	O
se	O
gayi	O
is	O
chota	O
gaye	O
pakistan	B-LOC
adalat	O
us	O
dissolution	O
ke	O
ballot	O
sifarshi	O
wahan	O
ek	O
the	O
keh	O
nay	O
adalat	O
jama	O
protest	O
gaya	O
coalition	O
sab	O
yeh	O
agar	O
rahi	O
char	O
the	O
aj	O
se	O
kuch	O
nomination	O
vote	O
constitution	O
protest	O
lakh	O
rahe	O
wazir	O
imran	O
sab	O
pta	O
pakistan	B-LOC
political	O
cabinet	O
the	O
sovereignty	O
aur	O
hakumat	O
tehsil	O
nazim	O
nizam	O
opposition	O
thi	O
tahaffuz	O
kal	O
president	O
par	O
president	O
intikhabat	O
ittehad	O
woh	O
aj	O
ilaqah	O
lahore	B-LOC
woh	O
accountability	O
mansoob	O
pakistan	B-LOC
nizam	O
bhi	O
election	O
corruption	O
crore	O
leader	O
char	O
naya	O
woh	O
sau	O
hakumat	O
yeh	O
judiciary	O
hai	O
ya	O
governance	O
sau	O
aj	O
the	O
democracy	O
par	O
sab	O
wazir	O
aj	O
parliament	O
kuch	O
qanoon	O
magar	O
tab	O
mein	O
purana	O
hain	O
government	O
political	O
speaker	O
magar	O
imran	O
constitution	O
us	O

campaign	O
ne	O
gaya	O
lahore	B-LOC
zilah	O
yahan	O
yeh	O
accountability	O
nab	B-ORG
ballot	O
hakumat	O
karachi	B-LOC
dissolution	O
jo	O
ilaqah	O
rahe	O
imran	O
teen	O
party	O
bhutto	O
aur	O
transparency	O
acha	O
ki	O
mansoob	O
karachi	B-LOC
panch	O
zardari	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ecp	O
the	O
imran	O
kiya	O
nizam	O
policy	O
do	O
islamabad	B-LOC
nay	O
election	O
tehsil	O
crore	O
acha	O
reform	O
pta	O
election	O
ko	O
lekin	O
purana	O
wazir	O
ek	O
tehsil	O
political	O
alliance	O
haqooq	O
ya	O
hain	O
bara	O
imran	O
magar	O
bara	O
nizam	O
hain	O
agar	O
jama	O
ke	O
speaker	O
rahi	O
manifesto	O
minister	O
provincial	O
muariza	O
party	O
bura	O
ecp	O
rahi	O
accountability	O
bahut	O
leader	O
islamabad	B-LOC
reform	O
woh	O
phir	O
bhutto	O
sau	O
parliament	O
kiya	O
to	O
nay	O
sahib	O
wahan	O
kuch	O
bhi	O
manifesto	O
ko	O
minister	O
to	O
tehreek	O
sahib	O
wahan	O
tehreek	O
rahe	O
rahi	O
ne	O
party	O
sab	O
par	O
pakistan	B-LOC
panch	O
agar	O
yeh	O
ilaqah	O
hai	O
musharraf	O
nab	B-ORG
cabinet	O
par	O
ne	O
rehbar	O
magar	O
ilaqah	O
political	O
zyada	O
opposition	O
musharraf	O
islamabad	B-LOC
hakumat	O
aur	O
ilaqah	O
vote	O
lakh	O
panch	O
gaye	O
kal	O
governance	O
accountability	O
yahan	O
sab	O
musharraf	O
ko	O
jumhuriat	O
judiciary	O
gaya	O
hain	O
rahi	O
wazeer	O
ki	O
bura	O
char	O
parliament	O
kuch	O
governance	O
chancellor	O
nab	B-ORG
premier	O
kuch	O
kam	O
bhutto	O
kam	O
nay	O
mein	O
manifesto	O
mansoob	O
hukumat	O
umeedwar	O
lakh	O
ki	O
tenure	O
kuch	O
sab	O
keh	O
yeh	O
nawaz	O
tenure	O
yeh	O
us	O
agar	O
constitution	O

gayi	O
trade	O
woh	O
keh	O
teen	O
phir	O
lahore	B-LOC
hain	O
kiya	O
zyada	O
economy	O
aur	O
bara	O
naya	O
nay	O
gaya	O
foreign	O
bajat	O
pakistan	B-LOC
woh	O
kuch	O
ya	O
budget	O
hain	O
zyada	O
amdaani	O
do	O
maeeshat	O
hain	O
reserve	O
monetary	O
wahan	O
to	O
daulat	O
bhi	O
mehngai	O
sbp	O
us	O
budget	O
quarter	O
kasad	O
gaya	O
do	O
jab	O
ek	O
teen	O
deficit	O
lakh	O
subsidy	O
rahi	O
remittance	O
teen	O
aur	O
honay	O
karachi	B-LOC
maaliyat	O
currency	O
growth	O
bond	O
secp	O
bura	O
kal	O
ya	O
market	O
services	O
gharibi	O
employment	O
bajat	O
economy	O
lakh	O
mehngai	O
kam	O
wazarat	O
bahut	O
us	O
mein	O
yeh	O
maaliyat	O
ko	O
jab	O
bond	O
ne	O
gaya	O
kal	O
ameer	O
wazarat	O
exports	O
deficit	O
market	O
aur	O
kiya	O
wage	O
foreign	O
to	O
ab	O
lekin	O
stock	O
wazarat	O
se	O
ab	O
ko	O
invest	O
loan	O
industrial	O
maaliyat	O
exchange	O
kam	O
acha	O
surplus	O
exchange	O
bura	O
hai	O
bahut	O
loan	O
kam	O
ya	O
bahut	O
takhlees	O
monetary	O
sbp	O
mehngai	O
mazdoor	O
gayi	O
currency	O
bhi	O
debt	O
karachi	B-LOC
is	O
kal	O
kiya	O
ya	O
industrial	O
honay	O
lekin	O
baat	O
kuch	O
quarter	O
secp	O
gayi	O
mazdoor	O
kuch	O
ne	O
poverty	O
rozgar	O
mazdoor	O
teen	O
char	O
kasad	O
panch	O
invest	O
quarter	O
to	O
agriculture	O
phir	O
industrial	O
bara	O
do	O
ki	O
us	O
kiya	O
buniyad	O
quarter	O
rupee	O
loan	O
gayi	O
kharchay	O
lekin	O
yeh	O
ek	O
maaliyat	O
wazarat	O
kiya	O
equity	O
tha	O
ab	O
monetary	O
bura	O
maeeshat	O
maal	O
tijari	O
economy	O
dollar	O
yeh	O
kasad	O
keh	O
maal	O
exchange	O
mehngai	O
keh	O
employment	O
wage	O
dollar	O
currency	O
pakistan	B-LOC
investment	O
services	O
zyada	O
invest	O
qarz	O
services	O
unemployment	O
maal	O
gaye	O
maeeshat	O
jo	O
bank	O
equity	O
nay	O
rahi	O
kiya	O
the	O
reserve	O
daulat	O
hazar	O
wazarat	O
yeh	O
agriculture	O
is	O
chota	O
trade	O
hai	O
currency	O
us	O
ka	O
panch	O
unemployment	O
services	O
ko	O
takhlees	O
tijari	O
yeh	O
budget	O
bhi	O
kuch	O
nay	O
hain	O
bara	O
tijarat	O
bhi	O
invest	O
bara	O
lakh	O
is	O
teen	O
bank	O
kam	O
yahan	O
wahan	O
to	O
paisah	O
ki	O
sau	O
rupee	O
deficit	O
gharibi	O
par	O
pakistan	B-LOC
bond	O
qarz	O
tijarat	O
raha	O
surplus	O
tariff	O
revenue	O
gaye	O
to	O
mein	O
bond	O
lekin	O
bond	O
currency	O
imports	O
purana	O
karachi	B-LOC
taxation	O
lahore	B-LOC
aur	O
aur	O
yahan	O
paisah	O
lakh	O
yeh	O
karza	O
qarz	O
takhlees	O
lakh	O
bura	O
hai	O
inflation	O
manufacturing	O
nay	O
market	O

to	O
pakistan	B-LOC
world	O
tournament	O
zyada	O
lakh	O
sau	O
ka	O
kam	O
muqabla	O
imran	O
phir	O
pitch	O
lahore	B-LOC
pacer	O
kiya	O
aj	O
raha	O
wahan	O
aj	O
rahi	O
pcb	B-ORG
player	O
tab	O
waqar	O
halfcentury	O
kuch	O
t20	O
char	O
multan	B-LOC
naya	O
the	O
thi	O
iqbal	O
naseem	O
wasim	O
honay	O
wicket	O
gaya	O
shaheen	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
nay	O
rahe	O
woh	O
tournament	O
peshawar	B-LOC
kam	O
karachi	B-LOC
shoaib	O
gayi	O
multan	B-LOC
tournament	O
sialkot	B-LOC
khel	O
ab	O
hai	O
lahore	B-LOC
bahut	O
ne	O
ki	O
agar	O
karachi	B-LOC
tab	O
stadium	O
khel	O
sau	O
karachi	B-LOC
khel	O
tha	O
yeh	O
batting	O
bowling	O
captain	O
thi	O
panch	O
jab	O
honay	O
jab	O
squad	O
psl	B-ORG
odi	O
panch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
naya	O
is	O
lahore	B-LOC
multan	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
rahe	O
hai	O
wasim	O
chota	O
selection	O
to	O
aur	O
magar	O
zaheer	O
spinner	O
inzamam	O
aur	O
us	O
run	O
selection	O
world	O
jab	O
ka	O
lakh	O
wahan	O
babar	O
series	O
century	O
lahore	B-LOC
world	O
crore	O
icc	B-ORG
the	O
hain	O
batting	O
naseem	O
australia	O
waqar	O
kiya	O
player	O
phir	O
zyada	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
hain	O
trophy	O
ko	O
t20	O
karachi	B-LOC
lahore	B-LOC
ne	O
cup	O
india	B-LOC
england	O
champion	O
lahore	B-LOC
india	B-LOC
maidan	O
odi	O
jo	O
bhi	O
gaddafi	O
team	O
wahan	O
lakh	O
goaal	O
pitch	O
phir	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
nay	O
gaya	O
pacer	O
teen	O
trophy	O
karachi	B-LOC
teen	O
waqar	O
keh	O
kam	O
bura	O
trophee	O
aur	O
fielding	O
pacer	O
cup	O
teen	O
khilari	O
fielding	O
jab	O
kam	O
bura	O
pakistan	B-LOC
multan	B-LOC
lahore	B-LOC
ya	O
captain	O
bahut	O

acha	O
crore	O
khilari	O
lekin	O
mein	O
fielding	O
se	O
shoaib	O
shaheen	O
haarna	O
pitch	O
purana	O
sab	O
panch	O
khilari	O
se	O
bara	O
khelna	O
the	O
sab	O
batting	O
selection	O
iqbal	O
pakistan	B-LOC
champion	O
haarna	O
world	O
muqabla	O
player	O
icc	B-ORG
psl	B-ORG
acha	O
inzamam	O
is	O
batting	O
score	O
kal	O
the	O
maidan	O
batting	O
tournament	O
crore	O
aur	O
wasim	O
babar	O
spinner	O
the	O
ki	O
maidan	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
iqbal	O
aur	O
bura	O
naya	O
captain	O
agar	O
coach	O
squad	O
rizwan	O
panch	O
raha	O
thi	O
allrounder	O
match	O
yahan	O
multan	B-LOC
khilari	O
agar	O
kal	O
woh	O
ka	O
karachi	B-LOC
younis	O
to	O
boundary	O
lahore	B-LOC
world	O
boundary	O
aur	O
nay	O
jab	O
crore	O
league	O
bhi	O
iqbal	O
sau	O
lahore	B-LOC
tha	O
pcb	B-ORG
misbah	O
tha	O
iqbal	O
gaye	O
kaptaan	O
team	O
to	O
islamabad	B-LOC
muqabla	O
cricket	O
khel	O
spinner	O
world	O
ek	O
honay	O
captain	O
waqar	O
is	O
tournament	O
honay	O
bahut	O
wicket	O
quetta	B-LOC
world	O
yeh	O
series	O
kal	O
squad	O
jo	O
shaheen	O
khel	O
team	O
spinner	O
wahan	O
lakh	O
to	O
lahore	B-LOC
jeetnay	O
panch	O
stadium	O
wasim	O
boundary	O
trophy	O
opener	O
aur	O
captain	O
ab	O
magar	O
yahan	O
purana	O
aur	O
lahore	B-LOC
babar	O
trophy	O
ke	O
ki	O
jo	O
quetta	B-LOC
misbah	O
do	O
peshawar	B-LOC
stadium	O
opener	O
se	O
gaddafi	O
is	O
world	O
gaye	O
agar	O
kuch	O
bhi	O
karachi	B-LOC
lakh	O
pacer	O
maidan	O
rizwan	O
ko	O
gaye	O
us	O
sialkot	B-LOC
kaptaan	O
sab	O
cup	O
multan	B-LOC
kal	O
bara	O
waqar	O
kal	O
bharat	O
wasim	O
inzamam	O
lekin	O
thi	O
raha	O
panch	O
world	O
bura	O
chota	O
bura	O
younis	O
karachi	B-LOC
over	O
ko	O
bahut	O
kaptaan	O
tab	O
bura	O
allrounder	O
psl	B-ORG
kiya	O
purana	O
mein	O
maidan	O
over	O
do	O
bhi	O
hai	O
ki	O
lahore	B-LOC
india	B-LOC
wicket	O
magar	O
yeh	O
trophee	O
bahut	O
team	O
rahe	O
se	O
imran	O
halfcentury	O
younis	O
shoaib	O
ek	O
odi	O
par	O
zyada	O
purana	O
boundary	O
cricket	O
world	O
se	O
lekin	O
acha	O
waqar	O
afridi	O
ki	O
world	O
zyada	O
gayi	O
gaya	O
imran	O
woh	O
misbah	O
kiya	O
babar	O
player	O
kam	O
yahan	O
allrounder	O
icc	B-ORG
magar	O
aj	O
coach	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
tab	O
nay	O
ek	O
t20	O
ke	O
ab	O
selection	O
to	O
gayi	O
is	O
teen	O
ki	O
afridi	O
england	O
score	O
afridi	O
iqbal	O
waqar	O
hain	O
par	O
world	O
maidan	O
trophee	O
lakh	O
chota	O
kuch	O
gaye	O
tournament	O
quetta	B-LOC
ab	O
acha	O
ek	O

teen	O
haarna	O
agar	O
bara	O
raha	O
tab	O
char	O
kal	O
team	O
char	O
bhi	O
goaal	O
gaye	O
jo	O
england	O
rizwan	O
cup	O
tha	O
player	O
par	O
odi	O
raha	O
ke	O
ya	O
tournament	O
sialkot	B-LOC
gaya	O
ko	O
khelna	O
panch	O
acha	O
karachi	B-LOC
kuch	O
thi	O
world	O
se	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
kaptaan	O
wasim	O
squad	O
ya	O
allrounder	O
hazar	O
aur	O
pcb	B-ORG
mein	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
gayi	O
team	O
islamabad	B-LOC
younis	O
keh	O
aj	O
zaheer	O
world	O
yahan	O
woh	O
karachi	B-LOC
odi	O
league	O
pacer	O
shoaib	O
naya	O
naseem	O
us	O
opener	O
shoaib	O
nay	O
gaye	O
char	O
t20	O
halfcentury	O
us	O
match	O
coach	O
trophee	O
khilari	O
world	O
lekin	O
kiya	O
iqbal	O
bahut	O
squad	O
trophy	O
panch	O
gaye	O
magar	O
aj	O
naseem	O
do	O
league	O
wicket	O
us	O
khilari	O
coach	O
world	O
tab	O
pitch	O
do	O
yeh	O
ko	O
bhi	O
psl	B-ORG
champion	O
gaya	O
do	O
wahan	O
coach	O
goaal	O
wicket	O
karachi	B-LOC
ab	O
hain	O
ko	O
bura	O
player	O
naseem	O
trophy	O
panch	O
shoaib	O
thi	O
agar	O
woh	O
icc	B-ORG
aj	O
karachi	B-LOC
goaal	O
crore	O
england	O
ke	O
pitch	O
team	O
jab	O
goaal	O
wahan	O
bara	O
sab	O
ek	O
wicket	O
the	O
coach	O
rahe	O
haarna	O
haarna	O
honay	O
agar	O
australia	O
younis	O
yeh	O
chota	O
honay	O
chota	O
rizwan	O
bowling	O
panch	O
odi	O
purana	O
raha	O
acha	O
khelna	O
trophy	O
yeh	O
par	O
agar	O
lahore	B-LOC
bharat	O
test	O
ya	O
rahe	O
pakistan	B-LOC
lahore	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
do	O
char	O
gayi	O
cup	O
magar	O
aur	O
ka	O
pakistan	B-LOC
mein	O
boundary	O
yeh	O
waqar	O
spinner	O
aur	O
raha	O
javed	O
match	O
odi	O
the	O
kiya	O
keh	O
aur	O
sau	O
team	O
league	O
karachi	B-LOC
peshawar	B-LOC
gaya	O
nay	O
thi	O
khelna	O
lakh	O

panch	O
rahe	O
ya	O
tijari	O
sbp	O
wage	O
islamabad	B-LOC
dollar	O
thi	O
wage	O
tha	O
ki	O
the	O
salary	O
tijari	O
naya	O
rate	O
do	O
rahi	O
gharibi	O
ab	O
hai	O
tab	O
budget	O
ke	O
bahut	O
bajat	O
purana	O
investment	O
currency	O
gaya	O
surplus	O
bhi	O
daulat	O
tha	O
bara	O
bura	O
us	O
lahore	B-LOC
maeeshat	O
aur	O
rate	O
raha	O
do	O
bara	O
sbp	O
gdp	O
daam	O
maaliyat	O
investment	O
us	O
kiya	O
fiscal	O
zyada	O
aj	O
honay	O
daam	O
tijari	O
karachi	B-LOC
daam	O
invest	O
lahore	B-LOC
ne	O
dollar	O
exports	O
stock	O
ne	O
hain	O
karachi	B-LOC
teen	O
bank	O
ek	O
currency	O
acha	O
imf	B-ORG
ke	O
maal	O
yeh	O
baat	O
crore	O
ameer	O
woh	O
exports	O
paisah	O
revenue	O
baat	O
us	O
thi	O
tariff	O
ko	O
ya	O
gharibi	O
kiya	O
sau	O
foreign	O
kasad	O
phir	O
pakistan	B-LOC
pakistan	B-LOC
sab	O
kam	O
stock	O
bank	O
mehngai	O
imf	B-ORG
ameer	O
budget	O
agar	O
pakistan	B-LOC
karachi	B-LOC
annual	O
dollar	O
surplus	O
sarmaya	O
keh	O
budget	O
income	O
rahe	O
is	O
magar	O
gaye	O
bahut	O
qarz	O
sab	O
lakh	O
kuch	O
par	O
equity	O
woh	O
jab	O
paisah	O
par	O
bura	O
wahan	O
secp	O
zyada	O
phir	O
ne	O
tha	O
privatisation	O
vikas	O
remittance	O
ki	O
karza	O
raha	O
rupee	O
ke	O
sab	O
qarz	O
daulat	O
tijarat	O
sarmaya	O
kasad	O
takhlees	O
phir	O
raha	O
islamabad	B-LOC
yeh	O
jab	O
to	O
panch	O
economy	O
tab	O
reserve	O
economy	O
pakistan	B-LOC
sab	O
karachi	B-LOC
services	O
panch	O
subsidy	O
market	O
salary	O
is	O
imf	B-ORG
sarmaya	O
daulat	O
kuch	O
mazdoor	O
maaliyat	O
vikas	O
services	O
exports	O
zyada	O
keh	O
bond	O
gdp	O
gayi	O
buniyad	O

char	O
keh	O
pakistan	B-LOC
hukumat	O
keh	O
do	O
hazar	O
nawaz	O
nomination	O
bahut	O
wazeer	O
nazim	O
panch	O
political	O
ya	O
zilah	O
tenure	O
yahan	O
sifarshi	O
jab	O
bhi	O
muariza	O
leader	O
ab	O
party	O
aj	O
political	O
do	O
rahe	O
lekin	O
is	O
leader	O
lekin	O
panch	O
jo	O
kiya	O
agar	O
karachi	B-LOC
lakh	O
federal	O
bahut	O
ecp	O
tehsil	O
nay	O
constitution	O
musharraf	O
campaign	O
ecp	O
gayi	O
assembly	O
constitution	O
insaf	O
coalition	O
ko	O
kam	O
bara	O
hakumat	O
jo	O
ballot	O
agar	O
lahore	B-LOC
lakh	O
raha	O
phir	O
ka	O
intekhab	O
ne	O
insaf	O
tehsil	O
accountability	O
yeh	O
zyada	O
chancellor	O
se	O
intekhab	O
zyada	O
awam	O
tanqeed	O
gayi	O
us	O
yeh	O
raha	O
naya	O
zardari	O
nay	O
policy	O
yeh	O
pta	O
honay	O
aur	O
yahan	O
nawaz	O
speaker	O
campaign	O
gayi	O
wahan	O
governance	O
sahib	O
ilaqah	O
is	O
ya	O
yeh	O

speaker	O
acha	O
judiciary	O
imran	O
tahaffuz	O
ne	O
ek	O
jama	O
sahib	O
zyada	O
is	O
se	O
jab	O
tab	O
gaya	O
political	O
hukumat	O
bahut	O
islamabad	B-LOC
honay	O
lekin	O
siyasat	O
jo	O
intekhab	O
president	O
kuch	O
tenure	O
is	O
mein	O
tehreek	O
rahe	O
zyada	O
hakumat	O
naya	O
cabinet	O
nazim	O
honay	O
char	O
chancellor	O
intekhab	O
accountability	O
insaf	O
adalat	O
ek	O
democracy	O
woh	O
ko	O
agar	O
committee	O
dissolution	O
ki	O
crore	O
wazeer	O
zyada	O
sifarshi	O
aur	O
chota	O
hazar	O
gaya	O
lakh	O
tha	O
thi	O
jab	O
ke	O
corruption	O
umeedwar	O
raees	O
assembly	O
keh	O
tha	O
jo	O
haqooq	O
mansoob	O
rahi	O
bura	O
tha	O
rehbar	O
kuch	O
ka	O
raha	O
rahe	O
thi	O
kal	O
mein	O
ek	O
yeh	O
mein	O
dissolution	O
to	O
campaign	O
tanqeed	O
keh	O
nomination	O
aur	O
alliance	O
manifesto	O
tahaffuz	O
nab	B-ORG
sovereignty	O
us	O
zilah	O
ne	O

india	B-LOC
bharat	O
gaddafi	O
acha	O
captain	O
nay	O
psl	B-ORG
ab	O
ek	O
wahan	O
keh	O
nay	O
world	O
india	B-LOC
match	O
ke	O
karachi	B-LOC
bharat	O
jab	O
wahan	O
woh	O
waqar	O
score	O
hai	O
fielding	O
naseem	O
naya	O
ka	O
goaal	O
player	O
purana	O
kal	O
chota	O
do	O
shaheen	O
hain	O
rahi	O
bhi	O
boundary	O
char	O
ek	O
bharat	O
chota	O
icc	B-ORG
is	O
pakistan	B-LOC
javed	O
aj	O
chota	O
bura	O
hai	O
teen	O
rahi	O
us	O
keh	O
team	O
team	O
match	O
honay	O
haarna	O
cricket	O
multan	B-LOC
bara	O
rahe	O
pakistan	B-LOC
bura	O
jab	O
naya	O
yeh	O
run	O
halfcentury	O
peshawar	B-LOC
team	O
younis	O
tha	O
batting	O
cricket	O
team	O
kal	O
bura	O
bharat	O
is	O
gaya	O
icc	B-ORG
jo	O
karachi	B-LOC
spinner	O
gayi	O
naya	O
tab	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
player	O
maidan	O
agar	O
spinner	O
hai	O
stadium	O
gaddafi	O
waqar	O
bowling	O
zaheer	O
run	O
jo	O
ab	O
tab	O
purana	O
run	O
thi	O
lahore	B-LOC
ke	O
kuch	O
ne	O
keh	O
england	O
sau	O
wahan	O
khelna	O
ko	O
bharat	O
muqabla	O
the	O
kuch	O
is	O
purana	O
pakistan	B-LOC
keh	O
lekin	O
england	O
rizwan	O
halfcentury	O
tournament	O
sialkot	B-LOC
younis	O
england	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
t20	O
bharat	O
mein	O
waqar	O
char	O
islamabad	B-LOC
purana	O
aj	O
inzamam	O
pakistan	B-LOC
peshawar	B-LOC
inzamam	O
thi	O
psl	B-ORG
peshawar	B-LOC
bharat	O
ek	O
tha	O
team	O
to	O
to	O
zaheer	O
wasim	O
coach	O
opener	O
ek	O
wasim	O
honay	O
league	O
waqar	O
magar	O
over	O
sau	O
jo	O
honay	O
gaddafi	O
halfcentury	O
score	O
us	O
rizwan	O
trophy	O

adalat	O
siyasi	O
parliament	O
nazim	O
acha	O
kam	O
gaya	O
aur	O
judiciary	O
reform	O
government	O
woh	O
nizam	O
awam	O
muariza	O
teen	O
the	O
se	O
corruption	O
acha	O
ko	O
democracy	O
umeedwar	O
do	O
adalat	O
thi	O
tab	O
parliament	O
lekin	O
nomination	O
jo	O
democracy	O
honay	O
nomination	O
vote	O
transparency	O
election	O
wazeer	O
yeh	O
coalition	O
sahib	O
par	O
aj	O
kuch	O
government	O
nazim	O
ya	O
naya	O
kal	O
bara	O
the	O
bahut	O
ne	O
chancellor	O
ballot	O
lekin	O
chota	O
bura	O
coalition	O
committee	O
hai	O
raha	O
pta	O
ab	O
aur	O
thi	O
committee	O
tehreek	O
protest	O
resign	O
is	O
pakistan	B-LOC
jumhuriat	O
phir	O
lahore	B-LOC
tab	O
sau	O
wahan	O
hukumat	O
kal	O
kam	O
hai	O
muariza	O
assembly	O
raees	O
keh	O
ne	O
constitution	O
keh	O
mein	O
protest	O
woh	O
do	O
ka	O
president	O
adalat	O
assembly	O
woh	O
magar	O
haqooq	O
rehbar	O
wazeer	O
do	O
sab	O
parliament	O
aj	O
wazeer	O
aj	O
naya	O
teen	O
jama	O
panch	O
intekhab	O
umeedwar	O
panch	O
ecp	O
aur	O
is	O
tab	O
phir	O
naya	O
aj	O
nab	B-ORG
premier	O
ko	O
federal	O
aur	O
yeh	O
nawaz	O
cabinet	O
ke	O
president	O
zilah	O
wahan	O
naya	O
qanoon	O
islamabad	B-LOC
naya	O
sifarshi	O
rehbar	O
nawaz	O
jab	O
cabinet	O
intekhab	O
rahi	O
gayi	O
lekin	O
magar	O
ki	O
muariza	O
corruption	O
nomination	O
intikhabat	O
assembly	O
hakumat	O
gaye	O
acha	O
sab	O
rehbar	O
intikhabat	O
lahore	B-LOC
tehsil	O
teen	O
ko	O
imran	O
phir	O
ki	O
bahut	O
gaya	O
imran	O
nab	B-ORG
us	O
cabinet	O
sau	O
sifarshi	O
rahi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ne	O
umeedwar	O
hazar	O
to	O
tha	O
tenure	O
rahe	O
sau	O
bhi	O
reform	O
teen	O
agar	O
accountability	O
rahe	O

growth	O
kharchay	O
budget	O
jo	O
gayi	O
ka	O
monetary	O
remittance	O
aur	O
teen	O
ko	O
rozgar	O
buniyad	O
wahan	O
zyada	O
ke	O
ek	O
par	O
takhlees	O
se	O
sab	O
qeemat	O
magar	O
rupee	O
rahe	O
unemployment	O
wage	O
buniyad	O
agriculture	O
ek	O
ka	O
us	O
panch	O
tab	O
takhlees	O
revenue	O
trade	O
lahore	B-LOC
hazar	O
lekin	O
ameer	O
bara	O
bajat	O
buniyad	O
ko	O
kuch	O
forex	O
bajat	O
buniyad	O
agar	O
wahan	O
debt	O
bahut	O
deficit	O
kam	O
forex	O
ab	O
raha	O
kam	O
foreign	O
mehngai	O
tha	O
keh	O
hazar	O
gdp	O
tab	O
services	O
poverty	O
currency	O
ka	O
kam	O
imports	O
bura	O
kam	O
tijari	O
yeh	O
kam	O
par	O
do	O
teen	O
to	O
trade	O
aur	O
fiscal	O
crore	O
invest	O
tab	O
panch	O
sau	O
lakh	O
imf	B-ORG
honay	O
wage	O
salary	O
manufacturing	O
surplus	O
taxation	O
jo	O
aur	O
crore	O
surplus	O
remittance	O
hain	O
char	O
wazarat	O
teen	O
naya	O
income	O
thi	O
tijarat	O
remittance	O
kuch	O
phir	O
rupee	O
daam	O
privatisation	O
zyada	O
qarz	O
gharibi	O
forex	O
income	O
crore	O
nay	O
tijarat	O
ka	O
kuch	O
zyada	O
acha	O
keh	O
aj	O
gharibi	O
honay	O
bajat	O
forex	O
chota	O
employment	O
ki	O
bura	O
to	O
ka	O
islamabad	B-LOC
kal	O
agar	O

team	O
magar	O
pcb	B-ORG
aur	O
wahan	O
kuch	O
jeetnay	O
woh	O
odi	O
spinner	O
bhi	O
sau	O
purana	O
thi	O
bara	O
wahan	O
iqbal	O
purana	O
honay	O
naseem	O
ko	O
hazar	O
icc	B-ORG
world	O
haarna	O
par	O
psl	B-ORG
stadium	O
karachi	B-LOC
sau	O
crore	O
par	O
ya	O
agar	O
wicket	O
lahore	B-LOC
trophy	O
bowling	O
squad	O
ke	O
team	O
thi	O
maidan	O
keh	O
se	O
tournament	O
test	O
wahan	O
selection	O
bara	O
shaheen	O
crore	O
teen	O
league	O
honay	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
bharat	O
ya	O
hain	O
ab	O
psl	B-ORG
multan	B-LOC
league	O
trophee	O
do	O
sialkot	B-LOC
champion	O
stadium	O
keh	O
bharat	O
is	O
us	O
goaal	O
spinner	O
to	O
mein	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
islamabad	B-LOC
kal	O
do	O
us	O
pitch	O
test	O
naya	O
char	O
keh	O
selection	O
zyada	O
ka	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
kal	O
rizwan	O
kiya	O
karachi	B-LOC
yahan	O
spinner	O
mein	O
ko	O
hain	O
kiya	O
lahore	B-LOC
keh	O
aj	O
gaya	O
kaptaan	O
australia	O
rahi	O
series	O
ab	O
halfcentury	O
iqbal	O
teen	O
kiya	O
afridi	O
jeetnay	O
the	O
lekin	O
bowling	O
sau	O
squad	O
tha	O
naseem	O
misbah	O
mein	O
keh	O
kaptaan	O
crore	O
pitch	O
teen	O
over	O
bhi	O
bhi	O
kiya	O
kaptaan	O
mein	O
gaye	O
kam	O
us	O
misbah	O
karachi	B-LOC
purana	O
pitch	O
score	O
bowling	O
ki	O
pitch	O
par	O
younis	O
afridi	O
woh	O
aur	O
zyada	O
boundary	O
bura	O
tha	O
stadium	O
is	O
squad	O
javed	O
ne	O
phir	O
t20	O
misbah	O
team	O
ki	O
aj	O

thi	O
nab	B-ORG
corruption	O
reform	O
karachi	B-LOC
agar	O
adalat	O
constitution	O
zilah	O
ballot	O
ya	O
teen	O
raha	O
woh	O
lekin	O
thi	O
tehsil	O
vote	O
rahi	O
siyasat	O
bhi	O
panch	O
ki	O
kal	O
raees	O
intekhab	O
raha	O
char	O
protest	O
lahore	B-LOC
siyasat	O
protest	O
dissolution	O
tehsil	O
hukumat	O
hukumat	O
jo	O
naya	O
purana	O
tehsil	O
sifarshi	O
hazar	O
political	O
raha	O
ya	O
intikhabat	O
speaker	O
speaker	O
hai	O
yeh	O
kam	O
kam	O
ecp	O
agar	O
aur	O
democracy	O
mansoob	O
keh	O
president	O
tehreek	O
accountability	O
teen	O
awam	O
naya	O
tab	O
ke	O
raees	O
imran	O
judiciary	O
nay	O
government	O
political	O
gaye	O
ke	O
resign	O
alliance	O
lekin	O
purana	O
ya	O
tanqeed	O
ke	O
raees	O
ittehad	O
nawaz	O
chancellor	O
governance	O
tanqeed	O
vote	O
aj	O
hai	O
kiya	O
dissolution	O
jab	O
alliance	O
panch	O
tehsil	O
transparency	O
rahi	O
policy	O
constitution	O
ek	O
the	O
jab	O
federal	O
to	O
jama	O
bhi	O
federal	O
honay	O
kuch	O
thi	O
kiya	O
musharraf	O
bhutto	O
sifarshi	O
panch	O
panch	O
gayi	O
siyasi	O
umeedwar	O
ab	O
resign	O
jab	O
nab	B-ORG
government	O
kuch	O
ek	O
mein	O
jumhuriat	O
purana	O
bura	O
bahut	O
premier	O
kal	O
yahan	O
hain	O
acha	O
ne	O
hazar	O
yahan	O
ne	O
islamabad	B-LOC
ko	O
jumhuriat	O
governance	O
keh	O
bahut	O
democracy	O
tab	O
acha	O
tanqeed	O
zilah	O
jab	O
accountability	O
woh	O
ek	O
ya	O
nawaz	O
bhi	O
qanoon	O
aur	O
aj	O
karachi	B-LOC
to	O
alliance	O
imran	O
agar	O
federal	O
democracy	O
transparency	O
acha	O
bhutto	O
policy	O
ka	O
ki	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ka	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ilaqah	O
bura	O
opposition	O
ka	O
sahib	O
tahaffuz	O
do	O
federal	O
speaker	O
pakistan	B-LOC
thi	O
senate	B-ORG
wazir	O
legislation	O
woh	O
gaye	O
ya	O
raha	O
alliance	O
bahut	O
mein	O
constitution	O
reform	O
do	O
se	O
tahaffuz	O
ya	O
keh	O
corruption	O
tehsil	O
gayi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
pakistan	B-LOC
is	O
panch	O
us	O
hakumat	O
bhi	O
do	O
sab	O
tenure	O
insaf	O
insaf	O
legislation	O
the	O
sahib	O
election	O
tenure	O
nazim	O
hai	O
us	O
dissolution	O
naya	O
hain	O
naya	O
adalat	O

us	O
asean	O
char	O
chota	O
russia	B-LOC
us	O
bahut	O
diplomacy	O
sco	B-LOC
alatifaq	O
muahida	O
bara	O
aj	O
hai	O
intifada	O
phir	O
intifada	O
honay	O
ek	O
tha	O
nato	B-ORG
ka	O
tab	O
india	B-LOC
jangi	O
se	O
panch	O
sco	B-LOC
mamlaat	O
bhi	O
agar	O
ki	O
honay	O
ne	O
jo	O
ka	O
hai	O
ya	O
thi	O
to	O
zyada	O
par	O
summit	O
chota	O
gaye	O
visit	O
trade	O
gaye	O
panch	O
aqwam	O
ajlasa	O
us	O
honay	O
ambassador	O
gayi	O
crore	O
relations	O
sco	B-LOC
summit	O
phir	O
purana	O
oic	B-ORG
cooperation	O
nuclear	O
nay	O
resolution	O
aj	O
embassy	O
ne	O
china	B-LOC
zyada	O
jangi	O
karachi	B-LOC
visit	O
alliance	O
ya	O
woh	O
sab	O
jo	O
chota	O
bhi	O
minister	O
mamlaat	O
panch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
zyada	O
hazar	O
chota	O
oic	B-ORG
jangi	O
peace	O
to	O
is	O
rahi	O
bhi	O
sanctions	O
se	O
keh	O
jab	O
embassy	O
india	B-LOC
se	O
honay	O
secretary	O
saudi	O
kam	O
diplomacy	O
ne	O
ajlasa	O
sulah	O
lakh	O
ke	O
gaya	O
oic	B-ORG
sco	B-LOC
tha	O
bahut	O
yahan	O
chota	O
bara	O
roznamcha	O
kal	O
muzakarat	O
se	O
naya	O
hai	O
humanitarian	O
china	B-LOC
wahan	O
security	O
jab	O
summit	O
yeh	O
roznamcha	O
bura	O
keh	O
jo	O
uae	B-LOC
to	O
agar	O
minister	O
saudi	O
cooperation	O
trade	O
border	O
jo	O
terrorism	O
yeh	O
roznamcha	O
zyada	O
foreign	O
islamabad	B-LOC
se	O
naya	O
hai	O
rahe	O
saarc	B-ORG
ka	O
thi	O
council	O
par	O
hazar	O
nato	B-ORG
bilateral	O
negotiations	O
border	O
bura	O
lekin	O
lekin	O
asean	O
islamabad	B-LOC
negotiations	O
roznamcha	O
kal	O
kuch	O
teen	O
phir	O
uk	B-LOC
panch	O
bainul	O
state	O
naya	O
russia	B-LOC
woh	O
crisis	O
iran	B-LOC
tab	O
lakh	O
panch	O
nay	O
ab	O
gayi	O
bahut	O
mamlaat	O
ki	O
kuch	O
lakh	O
sab	O

ne	O
the	O
honay	O
subsidy	O
income	O
debt	O
subsidy	O
currency	O
ab	O
mehngai	O
sau	O
bura	O
foreign	O
bura	O
lakh	O
kiya	O
agar	O
phir	O
tijarat	O
ki	O
remittance	O
buniyad	O
tha	O
ab	O
crore	O
salary	O
maal	O
raha	O
jab	O
secp	O
lakh	O
fiscal	O
subsidy	O
ka	O
inflation	O
maaliyat	O
kharchay	O
wage	O
lahore	B-LOC
kam	O
ka	O
employment	O
kuch	O
rupee	O
kasad	O
kam	O
us	O
mazdoor	O
maal	O
wahan	O
wahan	O
do	O
jo	O
ab	O
qarz	O
chota	O
subsidy	O
mein	O
dollar	O
woh	O
nay	O
salary	O
ko	O
thi	O
paisah	O
employment	O
rahi	O
amdaani	O
nay	O
par	O
employment	O
employment	O
tab	O
magar	O
honay	O
kam	O
tha	O
karachi	B-LOC
par	O
taxation	O
gayi	O
ko	O
ki	O
panch	O
manufacturing	O
stock	O
wazarat	O
tab	O
inflation	O
rate	O
se	O
mein	O
gaya	O
chota	O
hazar	O
sab	O
secp	O
maaliyat	O
rate	O
islamabad	B-LOC
char	O
hai	O
trade	O
kharchay	O
hazar	O
woh	O
sab	O
wazarat	O
magar	O
mein	O
investment	O
pakistan	B-LOC
raha	O
to	O
woh	O
char	O
hain	O
qarz	O
fiscal	O
ya	O
wahan	O
honay	O
reserve	O
manufacturing	O
raha	O
keh	O
to	O
buniyad	O
exports	O
vikas	O
unemployment	O
annual	O
ne	O
rahe	O
trade	O
baat	O
gaya	O
growth	O
kiya	O
revenue	O
equity	O
thi	O
budget	O
rupee	O
zyada	O
sarmaya	O
rate	O
to	O
mazdoor	O
investment	O
tijari	O
acha	O
gharibi	O
mein	O
rozgar	O
mehngai	O
mehngai	O
taxation	O
growth	O
income	O
lakh	O
foreign	O
lakh	O
par	O
hain	O
phir	O
kharchay	O
acha	O
purana	O
magar	O
kam	O
agar	O
tijari	O
nay	O
mazdoor	O
invest	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kharchay	O
dollar	O
maaliyat	O
invest	O
kuch	O
keh	O
bara	O
market	O
employment	O
gdp	O
forex	O
revenue	O
maeeshat	O
hazar	O
acha	O
tijari	O
poverty	O
rahi	O
bank	O
gaya	O
equity	O
rate	O
salary	O
ne	O
rupee	O
to	O
bahut	O
chota	O
economy	O
teen	O
ab	O
deficit	O
mein	O
the	O
par	O
growth	O
revenue	O
salary	O
ek	O
ka	O
unemployment	O
nay	O
panch	O
services	O
lakh	O
rahe	O
bhi	O
rahi	O
bond	O
lakh	O
kharchay	O
hai	O
raha	O
lekin	O
lekin	O
jo	O
rahi	O
chota	O
rahi	O
crore	O
keh	O
se	O
secp	O
yeh	O
daulat	O
kuch	O
agriculture	O
ke	O
thi	O
ke	O
invest	O
bhi	O
economy	O
ameer	O
do	O
is	O
exports	O
gaye	O
char	O
teen	O
char	O
mazdoor	O
bara	O
interest	O
daulat	O
imf	B-ORG
the	O

aj	O
sovereignty	O
nazim	O
wazir	O
policy	O
honay	O
jo	O
yeh	O
resign	O
zardari	O
ne	O
ki	O
hai	O
bhi	O
karachi	B-LOC
nomination	O
tenure	O
bura	O
yahan	O
naya	O
agar	O
musharraf	O
leader	O
intekhab	O
parliament	O
yeh	O
ilaqah	O
yahan	O
committee	O
speaker	O
mein	O
se	O
policy	O
jab	O
yeh	O
the	O
agar	O
kuch	O
wazeer	O
sau	O
imran	O
aj	O
purana	O
nay	O
gaya	O
ko	O
panch	O
gaye	O
raees	O
bura	O
agar	O
char	O
pta	O
lekin	O
aur	O
hai	O
jama	O
do	O
insaf	O
intikhabat	O
zilah	O
se	O
thi	O
hakumat	O
to	O
is	O
karachi	B-LOC
lekin	O
referendum	O
aur	O
bhi	O
karachi	B-LOC
awam	O
siyasi	O
ballot	O
premier	O
woh	O
sahib	O
islamabad	B-LOC
gaya	O
ke	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ke	O
ke	O
minister	O
muariza	O
raha	O
federal	O
jo	O
manifesto	O
sab	O
nay	O
rehbar	O
ka	O
jama	O
pta	O
provincial	O
bhutto	O
keh	O
hain	O
speaker	O
premier	O
qanoon	O
the	O
bahut	O
committee	O
chota	O
to	O
naya	O
bura	O
democracy	O
teen	O
policy	O
hai	O
lekin	O
se	O
wazir	O
nizam	O
aur	O
crore	O
jab	O
provincial	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
nazim	O
bura	O
siyasat	O
is	O
naya	O
qanoon	O
chancellor	O
tenure	O
raha	O
gaye	O
parliament	O
nay	O
lahore	B-LOC
yeh	O
the	O
karachi	B-LOC
premier	O
zardari	O
referendum	O
referendum	O
nomination	O
jumhuriat	O
gaya	O
referendum	O
karachi	B-LOC
adalat	O
cabinet	O
the	O
tenure	O
aj	O
judiciary	O
umeedwar	O
magar	O
islamabad	B-LOC
protest	O
ek	O
kam	O
gaye	O
gaya	O
reform	O
tehsil	O
magar	O
hazar	O
agar	O
sifarshi	O
bura	O
bara	O
aur	O
magar	O
kal	O
adalat	O
musharraf	O
referendum	O
ka	O
islamabad	B-LOC
provincial	O
referendum	O
wazir	O
nay	O
do	O
the	O
aj	O
islamabad	B-LOC
teen	O
sab	O
tahaffuz	O
naya	O
the	O
honay	O
se	O
us	O
mansoob	O
corruption	O
party	O
acha	O
hain	O
hai	O
us	O
jab	O
ke	O
ittehad	O
constitution	O
thi	O
ab	O
kam	O
accountability	O
assembly	O

aj	O
khel	O
khilari	O
rizwan	O
ek	O
ko	O
ka	O
afridi	O
sialkot	B-LOC
trophy	O
ko	O
world	O
bahut	O
char	O
muqabla	O
khilari	O
woh	O
goaal	O
rizwan	O
wasim	O
allrounder	O
gaddafi	O
jo	O
kiya	O
cup	O
ne	O
bura	O
imran	O
player	O
raha	O
series	O
ka	O
rahi	O
match	O
ab	O
fielding	O
do	O
rizwan	O
afridi	O
younis	O
jo	O
honay	O
bara	O
ki	O
iqbal	O
acha	O
phir	O
ab	O
zaheer	O
jo	O
gaye	O
kal	O
wasim	O
par	O
hazar	O
kal	O
fielding	O
hain	O
khelna	O
misbah	O
ab	O
tab	O
odi	O
jab	O
imran	O
coach	O
babar	O
hai	O
khilari	O
crore	O
purana	O
bura	O
khilari	O
trophy	O
india	B-LOC
tab	O
ka	O
league	O
wahan	O
honay	O
rahe	O
hazar	O
aur	O
magar	O
opener	O
hazar	O
teen	O
imran	O
trophy	O
zyada	O
multan	B-LOC
khilari	O
ko	O
keh	O
wahan	O
trophy	O
selection	O
halfcentury	O
aj	O
australia	O
javed	O
psl	B-ORG
odi	O
ab	O
wahan	O
batting	O
to	O
ya	O
boundary	O
bara	O
gaye	O
younis	O
ek	O
jab	O
squad	O
zyada	O
teen	O
gaya	O
peshawar	B-LOC
coach	O
chota	O
test	O
pitch	O
opener	O
waqar	O
gaddafi	O
ki	O
yeh	O
khel	O
psl	B-ORG
gaddafi	O
naya	O
wicket	O
icc	B-ORG
par	O
jo	O
agar	O
stadium	O
coach	O
woh	O
char	O
batting	O
us	O
bara	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ab	O
rizwan	O
tha	O
par	O
wicket	O
tab	O
sab	O
captain	O
sau	O
muqabla	O
wahan	O
magar	O
babar	O
teen	O
selection	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
waqar	O
chota	O
phir	O
aur	O
jo	O
wicket	O
lekin	O
world	O
sab	O
keh	O
lakh	O
khilari	O
shaheen	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
batting	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
yeh	O
bara	O
panch	O
team	O
squad	O
ab	O
karachi	B-LOC
babar	O
thi	O
coach	O
gayi	O
gayi	O
aur	O
india	B-LOC
t20	O
teen	O
tournament	O
yahan	O
se	O
ki	O
bhi	O
ko	O
world	O
trophy	O
zaheer	O
acha	O
hai	O
coach	O
cup	O
ab	O
ki	O
score	O
ki	O
aj	O
stadium	O
shaheen	O
batting	O
misbah	O
honay	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kam	O
babar	O
bhi	O
kal	O
kam	O
maidan	O
fielding	O
icc	B-ORG
muqabla	O
tournament	O
nay	O
ek	O
run	O
keh	O
acha	O
t20	O
ka	O

inflation	O
par	O
ya	O
income	O
ab	O
vikas	O
fiscal	O
sbp	O
annual	O
paisah	O
budget	O
ya	O
tariff	O
gayi	O
taxation	O
phir	O
debt	O
chota	O
imf	B-ORG
sarmaya	O
rahe	O
aur	O
agar	O
honay	O
gayi	O
vikas	O
thi	O
bajat	O
kam	O
buniyad	O
foreign	O
do	O
ek	O
growth	O
services	O
sab	O
kal	O
gaye	O
annual	O
mehngai	O
dollar	O
wage	O
investment	O
daulat	O
the	O
gaya	O
yahan	O
qeemat	O
bhi	O
kuch	O
privatisation	O
aur	O
acha	O
teen	O
fiscal	O
teen	O
equity	O
jab	O
us	O
gdp	O
sau	O
subsidy	O
lakh	O
jo	O
teen	O
yahan	O
hazar	O
yahan	O
do	O
poverty	O
kuch	O
gaya	O
se	O
invest	O
bahut	O
bank	O
currency	O
salary	O
is	O
ki	O
maal	O
crore	O
sab	O
investment	O
tab	O
wahan	O
teen	O
naya	O
rozgar	O
islamabad	B-LOC
rozgar	O
thi	O
hain	O
monetary	O
agar	O
woh	O
ek	O
karachi	B-LOC
karza	O
purana	O
forex	O
qeemat	O
jab	O
gdp	O
invest	O
mein	O
maeeshat	O
sab	O
lahore	B-LOC
aur	O
jab	O
purana	O
pakistan	B-LOC
paisah	O
crore	O
raha	O
buniyad	O
reserve	O
sarmaya	O
hain	O
mehngai	O
tijarat	O
kuch	O
purana	O
bhi	O
rahi	O
do	O
to	O
wahan	O
islamabad	B-LOC
salary	O
sarmaya	O
yahan	O
fiscal	O
annual	O
maeeshat	O
par	O
ne	O
keh	O
karza	O
deficit	O

kiya	O
ka	O
purana	O
teen	O
rahi	O
tanqeed	O
kiya	O
speaker	O
qanoon	O
yeh	O
assembly	O
ke	O
us	O
nawaz	O
premier	O
ek	O
ek	O
adalat	O
qanoon	O
constitution	O
accountability	O
governance	O
zyada	O
party	O
to	O
ka	O
pakistan	B-LOC
sab	O
nawaz	O
provincial	O
ecp	O
yeh	O
awam	O
rahi	O
to	O
teen	O
bahut	O
jumhuriat	O
referendum	O
ke	O
sovereignty	O
wazeer	O
ya	O
phir	O
ko	O
wazeer	O
phir	O
yahan	O
jab	O
bhutto	O
panch	O
sau	O
karachi	B-LOC
par	O
sahib	O
raees	O
crore	O
sahib	O
zardari	O
ittehad	O
do	O
nab	B-ORG
ya	O
kam	O
insaf	O
raha	O
kiya	O
rahe	O
government	O
hai	O
hai	O
imran	O
aur	O
naya	O
lekin	O
wazeer	O
se	O
hai	O
gayi	O
president	O
lahore	B-LOC
tha	O
intekhab	O
naya	O
awam	O
par	O
legislation	O
ne	O
tehreek	O
siyasat	O
ne	O
ka	O
hazar	O
insaf	O
awam	O
provincial	O
nazim	O
intikhabat	O
political	O
raha	O
democracy	O
imran	O
kal	O
ne	O
ko	O
coalition	O
sifarshi	O
gayi	O
ke	O
is	O
vote	O
democracy	O
yahan	O
raees	O
jama	O
ka	O
referendum	O
woh	O
chota	O
hazar	O
kal	O
us	O
mein	O
provincial	O
tab	O
tha	O
islamabad	B-LOC
the	O
nawaz	O
wazir	O
jo	O
raees	O
campaign	O
ballot	O
premier	O
tha	O
aj	O
manifesto	O
ne	O
ecp	O
ab	O
bhutto	O
minister	O
chota	O
intikhabat	O
tha	O
lahore	B-LOC

purana	O
diabetes	O
jo	O
bijli	O
rahi	O
honay	O
the	O
gaya	O
cancer	O
health	O
ne	O
relief	O
aur	O
sau	O
heart	O
aspatal	O
doctor	O
kitab	O
water	O
bara	O
sahan	O
social	O
thi	O
water	O
bimari	O
literacy	O
jab	O
yeh	O
hospital	O
naya	O
crore	O
development	O
rahe	O
dengue	O
ko	O
kitab	O
rehan	O
literacy	O
kitab	O
shelter	O
doctor	O
raha	O
school	O
student	O
kam	O
malaria	O
bijli	O
sabhyata	O
social	O
ko	O
parhai	O
relief	O
hai	O
kitab	O
ya	O
heart	O
sabhyata	O
agar	O
bara	O
doctor	O
us	O
ki	O
bara	O
education	O
the	O
aspatal	O
fund	O
do	O
nutrition	O
doctor	O
bara	O
kal	O
jo	O
hazar	O
insaan	O
woh	O
ne	O
yahan	O
gaya	O
bimari	O
covid	O
sabhyata	O
bara	O
aur	O
bahut	O
taleem	O
covid	O
nutrition	O
gaye	O
bhi	O
panch	O
sarkardar	O
ek	O
polio	O
mortality	O
tha	O
mein	O
raha	O
poverty	O
doctor	O
mental	O
welfare	O
teen	O
yeh	O
to	O
ki	O
mortality	O
shagird	O
disaster	O
mental	O
bura	O
acha	O
kam	O
chota	O
polio	O
gaye	O
paani	O
shagird	O
rahe	O
do	O
kam	O
bara	O
rahi	O
ab	O
panch	O
doctor	O
ka	O
ko	O
par	O
acha	O
bura	O
water	O
social	O
ko	O
keh	O
qoum	O
sabhyata	O
agar	O
disease	O
hai	O
bura	O
ko	O
disease	O
ustaad	O
islamabad	B-LOC
yahan	O
lekin	O
university	O
ustaad	O
aspatal	O
mein	O
hain	O
qoum	O
social	O
is	O
gaye	O
student	O
medicine	O
raha	O
the	O
clinic	O
teen	O
mein	O
disease	O
zyada	O
woh	O
water	O
school	O
magar	O
insaan	O
bhi	O
qoum	O
jab	O
bara	O
char	O
ki	O
aman	O
mortality	O
lekin	O
panch	O
bachay	O
student	O
zyada	O
rahe	O
bijli	O
fund	O
do	O
wahan	O
relief	O
community	O
honay	O
literacy	O
doctor	O
honay	O
agar	O
nutrition	O
purana	O
bahut	O
curriculum	O
diabetes	O
teen	O
ka	O
lekin	O
the	O
cancer	O
diabetes	O
paani	O
yahan	O
to	O
sehat	O
teen	O
madrasa	O
keh	O
ilaj	O
diabetes	O
shelter	O
qoum	O
ne	O
hain	O
islamabad	B-LOC
gayi	O
university	O
polio	O
university	O
tab	O
mein	O
aman	O

ka	O
ab	O
t20	O
karachi	B-LOC
test	O
lakh	O
mein	O
t20	O
javed	O
ka	O
rawalpindi	B-LOC
gaye	O
phir	O
younis	O
purana	O
jab	O
naya	O
par	O
gaye	O
sialkot	B-LOC
teen	O
aj	O
trophee	O
inzamam	O
purana	O
lakh	O
lakh	O
coach	O
kam	O
rizwan	O
fielding	O
ne	O
acha	O
bara	O
kuch	O
tournament	O
run	O
purana	O
rahi	O
islamabad	B-LOC
t20	O
world	O
gaya	O
iqbal	O
ya	O
shaheen	O
spinner	O
spinner	O
naya	O
sab	O
rahi	O
keh	O
champion	O
ek	O
honay	O
us	O
ka	O
jab	O
hai	O
squad	O
naya	O
khel	O
india	B-LOC
gaya	O
gaye	O
phir	O
kaptaan	O
jab	O
mein	O
muqabla	O
jeetnay	O
team	O
hain	O
bara	O
team	O
bharat	O
odi	O
captain	O
gaya	O
ab	O
panch	O
kiya	O
rizwan	O
acha	O
the	O
lakh	O
iqbal	O
icc	B-ORG
panch	O
batting	O
ka	O
world	O
crore	O
lakh	O
yeh	O
psl	B-ORG
muqabla	O
crore	O
jeetnay	O
boundary	O
nay	O
lekin	O
wicket	O
jeetnay	O
hazar	O
zaheer	O
hazar	O
lahore	B-LOC
naya	O
karachi	B-LOC
over	O
opener	O
phir	O
psl	B-ORG
javed	O
khel	O
is	O
do	O
bara	O
is	O
agar	O
gaya	O
zaheer	O
waqar	O
bhi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
kiya	O
cricket	O
inzamam	O
islamabad	B-LOC
panch	O
t20	O
ko	O
trophee	O
par	O
psl	B-ORG
ka	O
lahore	B-LOC
imran	O
nay	O
run	O
allrounder	O
odi	O
test	O
karachi	B-LOC
keh	O
hain	O
lakh	O
thi	O
gaye	O
century	O
ko	O
muqabla	O
babar	O
agar	O
panch	O
stadium	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
england	O
misbah	O
inzamam	O
se	O
iqbal	O
crore	O
quetta	B-LOC
hai	O
rahi	O
the	O
bahut	O
trophy	O
aj	O
multan	B-LOC
bahut	O
zyada	O
gaddafi	O
gaye	O
allrounder	O
naya	O
india	B-LOC
pakistan	B-LOC
purana	O
bhi	O
jab	O
char	O
kam	O
squad	O
is	O
score	O
khel	O
haarna	O
lekin	O
bahut	O
chota	O
ki	O
match	O
selection	O
bhi	O

spinner	O
wahan	O
yeh	O
kal	O
hain	O
shoaib	O
sab	O
ek	O
aj	O
allrounder	O
khilari	O
psl	B-ORG
karachi	B-LOC
agar	O
england	O
australia	O
boundary	O
cup	O
trophee	O
fielding	O
magar	O
gayi	O
trophy	O
chota	O
gayi	O
coach	O
pacer	O
raha	O
raha	O
pitch	O
to	O
bharat	O
ya	O
rahe	O
misbah	O
batting	O
ne	O
kuch	O
fielding	O
halfcentury	O
allrounder	O
lahore	B-LOC
imran	O
shaheen	O
tab	O
run	O
trophy	O
mein	O
opener	O
ek	O
ko	O
raha	O
century	O
naseem	O
bowling	O
run	O
kam	O
batting	O
imran	O
pakistan	B-LOC
tha	O
squad	O
psl	B-ORG
wasim	O
over	O
world	O
tournament	O
hazar	O
bura	O
player	O
boundary	O
score	O
goaal	O
mein	O
honay	O
peshawar	B-LOC
ya	O
zaheer	O
chota	O
captain	O
league	O
stadium	O
sab	O
coach	O
kal	O
shaheen	O
boundary	O
honay	O
lakh	O
imran	O
world	O
century	O
lekin	O
chota	O
thi	O
psl	B-ORG
pitch	O
odi	O
yahan	O
league	O
bowling	O
kam	O
to	O
zyada	O
aur	O
lahore	B-LOC
se	O
quetta	B-LOC
coach	O
pakistan	B-LOC
selection	O
t20	O
gayi	O
keh	O
zyada	O
selection	O
crore	O
opener	O
hain	O
multan	B-LOC
gaddafi	O
shaheen	O
zaheer	O
halfcentury	O
hain	O
bara	O
pakistan	B-LOC
boundary	O
pakistan	B-LOC
imran	O
ka	O
hazar	O
psl	B-ORG
faisalabad	B-LOC
kiya	O
muqabla	O
jab	O
rahe	O
hazar	O
rahi	O
afridi	O
lahore	B-LOC
par	O
goaal	O
selection	O
us	O
woh	O
zaheer	O
score	O
maidan	O
india	B-LOC
woh	O
woh	O
karachi	B-LOC
psl	B-ORG
ne	O
gayi	O
islamabad	B-LOC
jo	O
captain	O
ki	O
hazar	O
yahan	O
jab	O
kal	O
allrounder	O
lahore	B-LOC
ki	O
trophee	O
honay	O
ne	O
coach	O
nay	O
chota	O
gayi	O
goaal	O
pakistan	B-LOC
century	O
rizwan	O
series	O
peshawar	B-LOC
gayi	O
islamabad	B-LOC
captain	O
rahe	O
nay	O
lahore	B-LOC
magar	O
lakh	O
the	O
hazar	O
kal	O
karachi	B-LOC
khelna	O
muqabla	O
se	O
crore	O
pakistan	B-LOC
agar	O
teen	O
se	O
kaptaan	O
trophee	O
lakh	O
ab	O
thi	O
gayi	O
magar	O
champion	O
lahore	B-LOC
purana	O
sialkot	B-LOC
ne	O
pacer	O
gayi	O
gaya	O
bhi	O
jo	O
bura	O
teen	O
t20	O
rahe	O
tha	O
ne	O
kiya	O
mein	O
gaya	O
magar	O
allrounder	O
ke	O
quetta	B-LOC
aur	O
chota	O
world	O
team	O
jeetnay	O
khilari	O
nay	O
gaddafi	O
haarna	O
tournament	O
bharat	O
ne	O
faisalabad	B-LOC
nay	O
mein	O
rizwan	O
honay	O
teen	O
bara	O
odi	O
kaptaan	O
pakistan	B-LOC
halfcentury	O
selection	O
tha	O
spinner	O
pakistan	B-LOC
rahe	O
gaye	O
selection	O
yahan	O
gaye	O
the	O
league	O
zyada	O
bhi	O
afridi	O
gaye	O
cup	O
score	O
jo	O
javed	O
nay	O
ke	O
tab	O
purana	O
pcb	B-ORG
keh	O
jab	O
kal	O
agar	O
peshawar	B-LOC
hazar	O
peshawar	B-LOC
cup	O
sialkot	B-LOC
hazar	O
raha	O
lekin	O
test	O
odi	O
wicket	O
gayi	O
nay	O

nay	O
judiciary	O
resign	O
nab	B-ORG
governance	O
constitution	O
nazim	O
provincial	O
nazim	O
accountability	O
party	O
pakistan	B-LOC
siyasi	O
char	O
yeh	O
pakistan	B-LOC
adalat	O
rahe	O
ab	O
crore	O
rahi	O
raha	O
islamabad	B-LOC
hazar	O
minister	O
political	O
haqooq	O
hukumat	O
ilaqah	O
ballot	O
federal	O
char	O
hazar	O
agar	O
lahore	B-LOC
hukumat	O
tenure	O
nomination	O
siyasi	O
mein	O
vote	O
siyasat	O
tehreek	O
rahi	O
bhi	O
ittehad	O
purana	O
yahan	O
wahan	O
coalition	O
sifarshi	O
rahe	O
accountability	O
aur	O
opposition	O
ki	O
parliament	O
ya	O
agar	O
ka	O
constitution	O
committee	O
gayi	O
ya	O
transparency	O
pakistan	B-LOC
aur	O
ka	O
us	O
yahan	O
purana	O
ilaqah	O
raees	O
sifarshi	O
party	O
crore	O
haqooq	O
umeedwar	O
legislation	O
dissolution	O
chota	O
gayi	O
the	O
hukumat	O
coalition	O
the	O
do	O
provincial	O
hain	O
ilaqah	O
campaign	O
jo	O
leader	O
tenure	O
sau	O
zyada	O
nizam	O
thi	O
do	O
hain	O
protest	O
party	O
ballot	O
muariza	O
yahan	O
raha	O
accountability	O
bahut	O
is	O
imran	O
sab	O
tenure	O
constitution	O
umeedwar	O
kiya	O
is	O
government	O
rahe	O
ab	O
campaign	O
lahore	B-LOC
federal	O
lahore	B-LOC
protest	O
ek	O
premier	O
tha	O
bura	O
tenure	O
ilaqah	O
mein	O
sab	O
panch	O
char	O
governance	O
hain	O
lakh	O
election	O
ne	O
qanoon	O
election	O
leader	O
kiya	O
sab	O
insaf	O
ko	O
teen	O
keh	O
sau	O
aj	O
rahi	O
judiciary	O
parliament	O
nizam	O
siyasi	O
policy	O
crore	O
lakh	O
parliament	O
nawaz	O
legislation	O
intekhab	O
mein	O
provincial	O
ka	O
mein	O
nay	O
qanoon	O
tanqeed	O
bara	O
naya	O
kiya	O
gayi	O
gayi	O
musharraf	O
lakh	O
ya	O
dissolution	O
wazeer	O
tahaffuz	O
dissolution	O
zyada	O
haqooq	O
wahan	O
musharraf	O
naya	O
mein	O
panch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
bura	O
nizam	O
premier	O
musharraf	O
chancellor	O
manifesto	O
sab	O
ka	O
bara	O
assembly	O
phir	O
chota	O
rahe	O
pakistan	B-LOC
honay	O
wazeer	O
tha	O
se	O
jab	O
kal	O
kiya	O
intikhabat	O
gaye	O
transparency	O
kuch	O
legislation	O
senate	B-ORG
lekin	O
assembly	O
rahi	O
cabinet	O
pta	O
aur	O

thi	O
kal	O
thi	O
zyada	O
interest	O
keh	O
lahore	B-LOC
thi	O
gaya	O
aur	O
to	O
aur	O
amdaani	O
maeeshat	O
services	O
investment	O
kam	O
annual	O
poverty	O
aur	O
nay	O
reserve	O
lekin	O
stock	O
bank	O
invest	O
bara	O
kasad	O
par	O
wage	O
teen	O
us	O
agar	O
pakistan	B-LOC
pakistan	B-LOC
economy	O
mehngai	O
secp	O
poverty	O
ne	O
agriculture	O
aur	O
ki	O
annual	O
employment	O
bhi	O
wahan	O
rozgar	O
jo	O
tab	O
aj	O
ya	O
ka	O
nay	O
rate	O
ne	O
ameer	O
jab	O
qarz	O
vikas	O
agriculture	O
yeh	O
the	O
amdaani	O
lahore	B-LOC
char	O
magar	O
ki	O
lakh	O
stock	O
kiya	O
gayi	O
bara	O
kal	O
tab	O
do	O
aur	O
bahut	O
jo	O
vikas	O
kal	O
ke	O
yeh	O
dollar	O
qeemat	O
debt	O
bank	O
growth	O
thi	O
lakh	O
tariff	O
thi	O
karachi	B-LOC
dollar	O
the	O
gdp	O
investment	O
bahut	O
ab	O
ameer	O
monetary	O
exports	O
keh	O
woh	O
salary	O
ameer	O
gayi	O
loan	O
gdp	O
agar	O
surplus	O
zyada	O
ek	O
acha	O
buniyad	O
ko	O
growth	O
stock	O
ya	O
yeh	O
gdp	O
revenue	O
ab	O
sau	O
vikas	O
market	O
aj	O
gaya	O
raha	O
ya	O
islamabad	B-LOC
acha	O
qarz	O
agar	O
magar	O
gdp	O
imf	B-ORG
agriculture	O
remittance	O
equity	O
rate	O
fiscal	O
magar	O
surplus	O
sarmaya	O
imf	B-ORG
income	O
panch	O
to	O
rahe	O
zyada	O
industrial	O

fund	O
disease	O
qoum	O
shagird	O
tha	O
disease	O
bura	O
agar	O
bimari	O
lahore	B-LOC
water	O
vaccine	O
child	O
community	O
ghar	O
raha	O
char	O
kitab	O
gayi	O
pakistan	B-LOC
gaye	O
kiya	O
tab	O
kuch	O
aman	O
ngo	O
clinic	O
islamabad	B-LOC
sau	O
welfare	O
bahut	O
do	O
ngo	O
dawa	O
raha	O
ngo	O
disaster	O
cancer	O
jo	O
kam	O
bara	O
khwateen	O
lakh	O
aj	O
lahore	B-LOC
sabhyata	O
dawa	O
ab	O
fund	O
relief	O
acha	O
diabetes	O
sehat	O
chota	O
lekin	O
phir	O
medicine	O
hazar	O
do	O
zyada	O
treatment	O
malaria	O
islamabad	B-LOC
college	O
social	O
yahan	O
who	B-ORG
school	O
gayi	O
clinic	O
relief	O
welfare	O
scholarship	O
raha	O
dawa	O
student	O
gayi	O
shagird	O
rahi	O
malaria	O
tab	O
sab	O
vaccine	O
teacher	O
purana	O
thi	O
relief	O
gaye	O
insaan	O
naya	O
university	O
sau	O
teacher	O
lekin	O
gaya	O
ghar	O
ki	O
diabetes	O
ngo	O
health	O
doctor	O
school	O
crore	O
kiya	O
hai	O
madrasa	O
scholarship	O
who	B-ORG
do	O
mental	O
sewage	O
ustaad	O
ki	O
lahore	B-LOC
panch	O
kal	O
degree	O
thi	O
rahe	O
who	B-ORG
sarkardar	O
doctor	O
curriculum	O
mein	O
medicine	O
bahut	O
malaria	O
panch	O
education	O
char	O
ne	O
islamabad	B-LOC
paani	O
do	O
vaccine	O
yahan	O
woh	O
aabadi	O
raha	O
ya	O
purana	O
ab	O
thi	O
crore	O
maternal	O
bachay	O
gayi	O
covid	O
community	O
ngo	O
se	O
ustaad	O
woh	O
college	O
gaya	O
parhai	O
do	O
mortality	O
kiya	O
tab	O
literacy	O
bura	O
mental	O
disaster	O
zyada	O
se	O
yeh	O
surgery	O
honay	O
development	O
gayi	O
aspatal	O
school	O
gaye	O
relief	O

lakh	O
services	O
naya	O
economy	O
dollar	O
woh	O
jab	O
chota	O
wahan	O
lekin	O
annual	O
bahut	O
taxation	O
tha	O
employment	O
naya	O
invest	O
panch	O
se	O
economy	O
woh	O
monetary	O
bara	O
the	O
wazarat	O
exports	O
mehngai	O
pakistan	B-LOC
annual	O
wage	O
honay	O
is	O
market	O
qarz	O
maal	O
baat	O
zyada	O
sarmaya	O
debt	O
paisah	O
currency	O
phir	O
bara	O
lekin	O
ke	O
tijarat	O
bond	O
maal	O
qeemat	O
industrial	O
currency	O
bond	O
aj	O
rupee	O
salary	O
par	O
phir	O
keh	O
lakh	O
ne	O
the	O
loan	O
magar	O
investment	O
income	O
thi	O
zyada	O
panch	O
ke	O
yeh	O
secp	O
takhlees	O
sab	O
gaya	O
equity	O
char	O
phir	O
zyada	O
to	O
equity	O
gaye	O
remittance	O
rahi	O
ab	O
lekin	O
pakistan	B-LOC
keh	O
trade	O
honay	O
forex	O
investment	O
bond	O
kharchay	O
char	O
panch	O
ya	O
to	O
ne	O
ko	O
hain	O
secp	O
investment	O
hain	O
thi	O
aj	O
tha	O
ke	O
hai	O
us	O
keh	O
bhi	O
islamabad	B-LOC
panch	O
employment	O
dollar	O
mein	O
hai	O
lahore	B-LOC
gdp	O
wage	O
daam	O
kasad	O
salary	O
purana	O
sau	O
hain	O
kam	O
privatisation	O
hain	O
gharibi	O
bahut	O
ameer	O
bhi	O

bara	O
interest	O
ab	O
privatisation	O
jo	O
gayi	O
par	O
acha	O
imports	O
crore	O
aur	O
monetary	O
kasad	O
gayi	O
kuch	O
deficit	O
aur	O
rahi	O
loan	O
nay	O
gharibi	O
wazarat	O
privatisation	O
qarz	O
agriculture	O
hai	O
annual	O
kam	O
lahore	B-LOC
daam	O
rahe	O
mehngai	O
ke	O
maal	O
inflation	O
maaliyat	O
reserve	O
sbp	O
invest	O
rupee	O
salary	O
annual	O
jo	O
mazdoor	O
rahi	O
bura	O
lekin	O
deficit	O
panch	O
inflation	O
kuch	O
is	O
teen	O
jo	O
privatisation	O
ko	O
crore	O
bank	O
bond	O
inflation	O
bura	O
salary	O
karza	O
market	O
ko	O
maal	O
monetary	O
char	O
hai	O
chota	O
rahe	O
sab	O
teen	O
sbp	O
tab	O
remittance	O
loan	O
mehngai	O
acha	O
acha	O
imports	O
currency	O
tha	O
baat	O
jo	O
gaya	O
zyada	O
hai	O
lahore	B-LOC
reserve	O
is	O
maeeshat	O
revenue	O
bajat	O
qarz	O
purana	O
raha	O
tariff	O
kal	O
tijarat	O
hazar	O
wahan	O
gdp	O
bajat	O
teen	O
economy	O
aur	O
rahe	O
poverty	O
ameer	O
karachi	B-LOC
equity	O
foreign	O
ab	O
takhlees	O
privatisation	O

loan	O
kal	O
kiya	O
tha	O
ameer	O
services	O
maeeshat	O
kasad	O
loan	O
taxation	O
kasad	O
se	O
sau	O
hai	O
bajat	O
yahan	O
do	O
investment	O
us	O
tijari	O
crore	O
wage	O
rahe	O
naya	O
monetary	O
kiya	O
lekin	O
agriculture	O
vikas	O
ko	O
annual	O
panch	O
yeh	O
phir	O
quarter	O
bara	O
tab	O
lahore	B-LOC
tab	O
gaye	O
maeeshat	O
gayi	O
imports	O
bura	O
agar	O
surplus	O
inflation	O
bahut	O
kiya	O
annual	O
foreign	O
ko	O
exchange	O
jab	O
trade	O
bank	O
lekin	O
reserve	O
karachi	B-LOC
raha	O
magar	O
qeemat	O
hazar	O
fiscal	O
employment	O
acha	O
tariff	O
kharchay	O
budget	O
bahut	O
panch	O
sarmaya	O
hai	O
wahan	O
tha	O
us	O
is	O
bajat	O
maaliyat	O
yahan	O
remittance	O
ne	O
salary	O
rozgar	O
gdp	O
ab	O
buniyad	O
sab	O
invest	O
bhi	O
exports	O
pakistan	B-LOC
daam	O
yahan	O
industrial	O
mehngai	O
ke	O
woh	O
jab	O
rahi	O
amdaani	O
invest	O
equity	O
amdaani	O
acha	O
crore	O
sab	O
agar	O
gaya	O
panch	O
income	O
taxation	O
annual	O
lakh	O
sab	O
ek	O
gdp	O
revenue	O
magar	O
lekin	O
tab	O
chota	O
annual	O
budget	O
kasad	O
unemployment	O
to	O
services	O
revenue	O
inflation	O
mazdoor	O
equity	O
tab	O
is	O
currency	O
maeeshat	O
yeh	O
foreign	O
mehngai	O
revenue	O
ameer	O
deficit	O
equity	O
gharibi	O
bajat	O
nay	O
remittance	O
takhlees	O
kharchay	O
inflation	O
debt	O
services	O
amdaani	O
reserve	O
exchange	O
the	O
tariff	O
ka	O
yahan	O
jo	O
ko	O
lakh	O
mehngai	O
buniyad	O
gharibi	O
kasad	O
crore	O
budget	O
hai	O
ne	O
qeemat	O
imf	B-ORG
quarter	O
ab	O
bara	O
yeh	O
kuch	O
pakistan	B-LOC
revenue	O
sab	O
hai	O
bahut	O
foreign	O
qeemat	O
bank	O
lahore	B-LOC
naya	O
gharibi	O
panch	O
bura	O
panch	O
chota	O
ek	O
rahi	O
aj	O
ab	O
remittance	O
chota	O
quarter	O
tijarat	O
mazdoor	O
rahi	O
tab	O
keh	O
ameer	O
ab	O
honay	O
inflation	O
crore	O
lahore	B-LOC
zyada	O
currency	O
mazdoor	O
foreign	O
tab	O
tijarat	O
bura	O
imports	O
rate	O
purana	O
bond	O
panch	O
remittance	O
unemployment	O
invest	O
tab	O
amdaani	O
rupee	O
vikas	O
rozgar	O
islamabad	B-LOC
sau	O
mehngai	O
invest	O
hain	O
tab	O
kuch	O
monetary	O
bajat	O
pakistan	B-LOC
sau	O
ameer	O
hain	O
invest	O
ya	O
mehngai	O
amdaani	O
tha	O
sau	O
purana	O
us	O
to	O
growth	O
magar	O
crore	O
aj	O
phir	O

do	O
lakh	O
manifesto	O
parliament	O
raha	O
ek	O
lahore	B-LOC
reform	O
nomination	O
siyasi	O
chota	O
ne	O
aj	O
purana	O
umeedwar	O
se	O
insaf	O
wazeer	O
legislation	O
constitution	O
par	O
kuch	O
agar	O
ek	O
kam	O
tehsil	O
crore	O
tha	O
jab	O
mein	O
honay	O
gaye	O
acha	O
teen	O
ecp	O
rahi	O
referendum	O
minister	O
nizam	O
protest	O
ko	O
se	O
karachi	B-LOC
nazim	O
lahore	B-LOC
raha	O
purana	O
tenure	O
par	O
phir	O
karachi	B-LOC
ya	O
bara	O
us	O
zyada	O
bara	O
agar	O
par	O
rahe	O
zyada	O
wahan	O
ka	O
aj	O
nab	B-ORG
provincial	O
nab	B-ORG
raha	O
ek	O
gayi	O
agar	O
federal	O
bhutto	O
wazeer	O
ne	O
gaya	O
raha	O
panch	O
ek	O
parliament	O
panch	O
teen	O
hai	O
jumhuriat	O
alliance	O
accountability	O
qanoon	O
judiciary	O
alliance	O
ya	O
lahore	B-LOC
islamabad	B-LOC
accountability	O
ittehad	O
gayi	O
honay	O
accountability	O
lahore	B-LOC
ballot	O
bura	O
alliance	O
wahan	O
lekin	O
transparency	O
zyada	O
thi	O
aur	O
aj	O
ke	O
kiya	O
raha	O
nomination	O
government	O
provincial	O
tehreek	O
se	O
do	O

pakistan	B-LOC
us	O
bhutto	O
imran	O
nab	B-ORG
political	O
par	O
yeh	O
speaker	O
ek	O
aj	O
acha	O
ki	O
sovereignty	O
ab	O
kal	O
jab	O
nazim	O
hakumat	O
awam	O
political	O
government	O
ka	O
tanqeed	O
honay	O
nay	O
protest	O
sau	O
ilaqah	O
hain	O
char	O
par	O
parliament	O
ittehad	O
kuch	O
tha	O
tanqeed	O
islamabad	B-LOC
pta	O
yahan	O
intekhab	O
gaya	O
lakh	O
bara	O
resign	O
wahan	O
mein	O
governance	O
ya	O
islamabad	B-LOC
hain	O
agar	O
yeh	O
phir	O
awam	O
premier	O
aj	O
coalition	O
parliament	O
pakistan	B-LOC
nomination	O
parliament	O
hazar	O
protest	O
kam	O
ke	O
chota	O
bhi	O
jab	O
bhutto	O
tehreek	O
kiya	O
ke	O
acha	O
lahore	B-LOC
pta	O
rahi	O
ne	O
accountability	O
do	O
imran	O
lahore	B-LOC
wahan	O
corruption	O
raha	O
thi	O
cabinet	O
se	O
jama	O
leader	O
wahan	O
kam	O
protest	O
vote	O
wahan	O
ki	O
woh	O
karachi	B-LOC
aur	O
to	O
agar	O
accountability	O
do	O
bara	O
election	O
the	O
yeh	O
sovereignty	O
accountability	O
sau	O
ya	O
sau	O
thi	O
ke	O
chancellor	O
sab	O
alliance	O
mein	O
kam	O
manifesto	O
umeedwar	O
nay	O
haqooq	O

sarmaya	O
maal	O
ko	O
jab	O
imports	O
bank	O
rahi	O
budget	O
teen	O
crore	O
tha	O
monetary	O
maal	O
rahe	O
maal	O
karza	O
exports	O
tab	O
hazar	O
secp	O
dollar	O
naya	O
maaliyat	O
panch	O
chota	O
income	O
yahan	O
ab	O
rahe	O
lahore	B-LOC
aj	O
gdp	O
ka	O
monetary	O
revenue	O
par	O
privatisation	O
the	O
economy	O
ek	O
sau	O
ne	O
lahore	B-LOC
mein	O
forex	O
exports	O
industrial	O
wahan	O
gayi	O
gaya	O
agriculture	O
tijarat	O
interest	O
mein	O
keh	O
exchange	O
remittance	O
buniyad	O
ab	O
interest	O
bahut	O
income	O
hazar	O
teen	O
income	O
mehngai	O
agar	O
to	O
growth	O
bahut	O
hai	O
surplus	O
bhi	O
dollar	O
ameer	O
rozgar	O
nay	O
the	O
karza	O
yahan	O
tha	O
hazar	O
growth	O
tha	O
trade	O
bond	O
sau	O
magar	O
raha	O
acha	O
acha	O
sbp	O
sau	O
keh	O
ek	O
services	O
bara	O
lahore	B-LOC
maal	O
invest	O
buniyad	O
manufacturing	O
monetary	O
pakistan	B-LOC
naya	O
woh	O
maeeshat	O
crore	O
equity	O
panch	O
subsidy	O
yahan	O
economy	O
hazar	O
tijarat	O
teen	O
hazar	O
interest	O
bura	O
amdaani	O
bura	O
tijari	O
remittance	O
lakh	O
phir	O
gaye	O
daam	O
takhlees	O
hain	O
tha	O
islamabad	B-LOC
bahut	O
chota	O
buniyad	O
growth	O
do	O
bank	O
tijarat	O
deficit	O
surplus	O
exchange	O
maal	O
kharchay	O
mehngai	O
lekin	O
subsidy	O
bajat	O
foreign	O
ek	O
agriculture	O
bank	O
yeh	O
bura	O
rupee	O
secp	O
quarter	O
deficit	O
chota	O
gaya	O
magar	O
trade	O
stock	O
surplus	O
phir	O
islamabad	B-LOC
teen	O
aj	O
revenue	O
se	O
employment	O
wazarat	O
do	O
chota	O
paisah	O
purana	O
maal	O
ka	O
keh	O
sau	O
growth	O
ko	O
rahi	O
fiscal	O
daam	O
lakh	O
ki	O
honay	O
remittance	O
gaye	O
agar	O
agar	O
naya	O
tab	O
hain	O
interest	O
ne	O
wahan	O
yahan	O
loan	O
gdp	O
trade	O
kharchay	O
subsidy	O
kuch	O
acha	O
trade	O
investment	O
tariff	O
ne	O
to	O
nay	O
ka	O
kal	O
ki	O
daam	O
buniyad	O
quarter	O
maeeshat	O
kuch	O
dollar	O
tab	O
unemployment	O
daulat	O
char	O
privatisation	O
gaye	O
agriculture	O
the	O
paisah	O
karachi	B-LOC
income	O
currency	O
takhlees	O
mein	O
ek	O
imf	B-ORG
se	O
mazdoor	O
pakistan	B-LOC
imports	O
gaya	O
kiya	O
is	O
thi	O
keh	O
se	O
qeemat	O
rahe	O
acha	O
hai	O
lahore	B-LOC
pakistan	B-LOC
gaye	O

bahut	O
gaye	O
crore	O
jo	O
teen	O
hain	O
adalat	O
bara	O
islamabad	B-LOC
teen	O
manifesto	O
assembly	O
ab	O
sab	O
gaye	O
hai	O
government	O
siyasat	O
wahan	O
hain	O
adalat	O
governance	O
chota	O
governance	O
bahut	O
jama	O
ya	O
ka	O
tenure	O
federal	O
kal	O
campaign	O
nazim	O
sau	O
kam	O
tehsil	O
sab	O
lakh	O
keh	O
jama	O
raha	O
keh	O
siyasat	O
ab	O
tehreek	O
ittehad	O
democracy	O
senate	B-ORG
bara	O
kal	O
char	O
yeh	O
resign	O
bara	O
bhutto	O
accountability	O
acha	O
pta	O
mein	O
protest	O
assembly	O
hain	O
thi	O
zyada	O
minister	O
do	O
agar	O
governance	O
ek	O
karachi	B-LOC
committee	O
kiya	O
siyasat	O
ke	O
pakistan	B-LOC
wazir	O
committee	O
magar	O
speaker	O
hazar	O
sab	O
tehsil	O
lakh	O
teen	O
panch	O
se	O
raha	O
tehsil	O
tenure	O
speaker	O
us	O
governance	O
kam	O
raees	O
lahore	B-LOC
jumhuriat	O
referendum	O
umeedwar	O
karachi	B-LOC
pta	O
yahan	O
accountability	O
coalition	O
tehsil	O
aj	O
umeedwar	O
yeh	O
nab	B-ORG
ecp	O
raees	O
tenure	O
president	O
gayi	O
coalition	O
mein	O
intekhab	O
tenure	O
sab	O
kal	O
governance	O
se	O
hukumat	O
adalat	O
zilah	O
opposition	O
bhutto	O
dissolution	O
coalition	O
wahan	O
gaya	O
kuch	O
mein	O
ne	O
governance	O
umeedwar	O
pta	O
intekhab	O
hukumat	O
nab	B-ORG
honay	O
hai	O
dissolution	O
naya	O
ki	O
parliament	O
sovereignty	O
bara	O
intekhab	O
manifesto	O
aj	O
ya	O
phir	O
hukumat	O
ab	O
rahe	O
assembly	O
char	O
kuch	O
aur	O
pakistan	B-LOC
election	O
the	O
do	O
gaye	O
assembly	O
aur	O
ilaqah	O
constitution	O
musharraf	O
chancellor	O
constitution	O
referendum	O
democracy	O
teen	O
par	O
chota	O
islamabad	B-LOC
aj	O
qanoon	O
aj	O
party	O
is	O
jo	O
panch	O
aj	O
ab	O
bahut	O
senate	B-ORG
cabinet	O
ko	O
mein	O

gaye	O
remittance	O
loan	O
lahore	B-LOC
poverty	O
kam	O
economy	O
acha	O
inflation	O
keh	O
karza	O
fiscal	O
exports	O
currency	O
islamabad	B-LOC
interest	O
imports	O
maal	O
salary	O
nay	O
acha	O
is	O
trade	O
equity	O
teen	O
agriculture	O
jo	O
bajat	O
mein	O
imf	B-ORG
naya	O
gaya	O
hai	O
kiya	O
par	O
yahan	O
inflation	O
maal	O
bara	O
bajat	O
kiya	O
jab	O
imf	B-ORG
gaye	O
lekin	O
the	O
paisah	O
crore	O
manufacturing	O
lahore	B-LOC
kasad	O
tariff	O
yahan	O
kasad	O
bond	O
bond	O
daulat	O
takhlees	O
agar	O
purana	O
agar	O
bura	O
surplus	O
sab	O
gayi	O
gayi	O
zyada	O
daulat	O
ya	O
ya	O
tab	O
gdp	O
agar	O
wahan	O
dollar	O
hain	O
gharibi	O
daam	O
us	O
honay	O
sarmaya	O
magar	O
takhlees	O
pakistan	B-LOC
teen	O
baat	O
wahan	O
thi	O
lakh	O
do	O
unemployment	O
monetary	O
crore	O
ko	O
ek	O
aj	O
vikas	O
sbp	O
bhi	O
karachi	B-LOC
ka	O
bura	O
gaya	O
vikas	O
inflation	O
kam	O
hain	O
jab	O
wazarat	O
ke	O
tha	O
phir	O
invest	O
jo	O
woh	O
lakh	O
raha	O
loan	O
lahore	B-LOC
wage	O
sarmaya	O
takhlees	O
kiya	O
rate	O
invest	O
industrial	O
karza	O
lakh	O
zyada	O
bhi	O
hain	O
subsidy	O
raha	O
woh	O
ne	O
inflation	O
maal	O
nay	O
is	O
karza	O
zyada	O
annual	O
kuch	O
bahut	O
chota	O
maeeshat	O
islamabad	B-LOC
employment	O
gaya	O
gaya	O
panch	O
foreign	O
se	O
remittance	O
mazdoor	O
ke	O
gdp	O
purana	O
nay	O
bank	O
sab	O
kal	O
kiya	O
ki	O
yahan	O
equity	O
phir	O
ke	O
amdaani	O
budget	O
economy	O
taxation	O
keh	O
panch	O
interest	O
kharchay	O
karachi	B-LOC
hain	O
tha	O
sbp	O
rozgar	O
daam	O
us	O
daam	O
purana	O
industrial	O
qeemat	O
ab	O
bhi	O
panch	O
the	O
qeemat	O
rahi	O
do	O
aur	O
mein	O
trade	O
gharibi	O
rupee	O
sau	O
ek	O
aj	O
yeh	O
aj	O
sab	O
yahan	O
ki	O
services	O
unemployment	O
rozgar	O
rupee	O
ki	O
tijari	O
keh	O

annual	O
se	O
gaya	O
purana	O
qeemat	O
zyada	O
maal	O
agar	O
imports	O
income	O
mazdoor	O
taxation	O
trade	O
teen	O
ke	O
ameer	O
thi	O
tijarat	O
kiya	O
imf	B-ORG
woh	O
kuch	O
aur	O
debt	O
bajat	O
aur	O
sau	O
gaye	O
ne	O
foreign	O
keh	O
ko	O
tijari	O
hazar	O
naya	O
services	O
maeeshat	O
ke	O
surplus	O
equity	O
ameer	O
crore	O
revenue	O
fiscal	O
exchange	O
teen	O
sarmaya	O
surplus	O
purana	O
sau	O
zyada	O
foreign	O
foreign	O
karza	O
tha	O
magar	O
economy	O
services	O
rahi	O
kasad	O
ek	O
aj	O
par	O
kiya	O
karachi	B-LOC
wahan	O
agriculture	O
islamabad	B-LOC
inflation	O
ko	O
zyada	O
wahan	O
tijarat	O
reserve	O
ne	O
jab	O
investment	O
tijarat	O
thi	O
wahan	O
acha	O
us	O
invest	O
services	O
magar	O
raha	O
baat	O
mein	O
maaliyat	O
the	O
hazar	O
economy	O
salary	O
dollar	O
remittance	O
crore	O
exports	O
to	O
amdaani	O
revenue	O
bara	O
qeemat	O
lekin	O
purana	O
bura	O
vikas	O
quarter	O
ne	O
bhi	O
bajat	O
agriculture	O
unemployment	O
ke	O
ke	O
foreign	O
gaya	O
bajat	O
karachi	B-LOC
jab	O
ab	O
privatisation	O
reserve	O
ek	O
buniyad	O
daulat	O
kharchay	O
kharchay	O
lekin	O
taxation	O
sau	O
karachi	B-LOC
acha	O
rate	O
investment	O
se	O
thi	O
forex	O
char	O
zyada	O
aj	O
par	O
market	O
jo	O
naya	O
rupee	O
bond	O
bahut	O
rate	O
sau	O
mazdoor	O
lakh	O
tha	O
services	O
lahore	B-LOC
ek	O
ab	O

ka	O
vikas	O
growth	O
qeemat	O
bhi	O
manufacturing	O
gayi	O
dollar	O
lahore	B-LOC
poverty	O
char	O
kam	O
wazarat	O
kiya	O
invest	O
char	O
reserve	O
se	O
kuch	O
tha	O
lekin	O
agriculture	O
maeeshat	O
rahi	O
sab	O
crore	O
baat	O
crore	O
investment	O
hain	O
services	O
gayi	O
keh	O
to	O
bara	O
ne	O
ab	O
annual	O
remittance	O
mehngai	O
deficit	O
income	O
privatisation	O
exchange	O
services	O
market	O
kal	O
tha	O
amdaani	O
zyada	O
lekin	O
par	O
interest	O
yeh	O
gdp	O
growth	O
hazar	O
karza	O
qarz	O
paisah	O
pakistan	B-LOC
ki	O
reserve	O
foreign	O
kiya	O
kal	O
rahe	O
jo	O
acha	O
sab	O
quarter	O
manufacturing	O
agar	O
imports	O
bajat	O
gharibi	O
interest	O
vikas	O
buniyad	O
bahut	O
karza	O
kharchay	O
quarter	O
privatisation	O
do	O
wage	O
daam	O
maaliyat	O
maaliyat	O
taxation	O
invest	O
gaya	O
wazarat	O
karachi	B-LOC
keh	O
ke	O
privatisation	O
amdaani	O
lahore	B-LOC
aj	O
revenue	O
ameer	O
invest	O
foreign	O
ab	O
investment	O
quarter	O
zyada	O
budget	O
keh	O
amdaani	O
chota	O
wage	O
fiscal	O
market	O
magar	O
honay	O
trade	O
bhi	O
revenue	O
quarter	O
gaye	O
keh	O
raha	O
mehngai	O
ke	O
purana	O
industrial	O
teen	O
growth	O
ka	O
char	O
kasad	O
kal	O
currency	O
kiya	O
hai	O
maal	O
bara	O
kal	O
bura	O
teen	O
ne	O
kal	O
currency	O
reserve	O
poverty	O
kam	O
wage	O
market	O
do	O
bhi	O
acha	O
salary	O
sau	O
exports	O
invest	O
naya	O
aur	O

ki	O
turkey	B-LOC
jab	O
intifada	O
border	O
nato	B-ORG
gaya	O
iran	B-LOC
sco	B-LOC
to	O
kal	O
yahan	O
aman	O
bura	O
gayi	O
foreign	O
lahore	B-LOC
purana	O
talks	O
russia	B-LOC
char	O
uk	B-LOC
sulah	O
sarhad	O
ke	O
iran	B-LOC
chota	O
gayi	O
hain	O
teen	O
ya	O
fauj	O
saudi	O
sarhad	O
wahan	O
to	O
peace	O
ya	O
woh	O
ki	O
kam	O
bura	O
gaye	O
nay	O
ya	O
naya	O
naya	O
mein	O
lekin	O
ceasefire	O
asean	O
sau	O
sco	B-LOC
ko	O
jangi	O
bahut	O
uk	B-LOC
nato	B-ORG
aur	O
ceasefire	O
aid	O
woh	O
bainul	O
diplomacy	O
alliance	O
thi	O
india	B-LOC
crisis	O
agreement	O
humanitarian	O
bilateral	O
hai	O
alatifaq	O
sarhad	O
iran	B-LOC
kal	O
woh	O
yahan	O
nuclear	O
bura	O
rahi	O
yahan	O
the	O
honay	O
foreign	O
purana	O
conflict	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
ke	O
islamabad	B-LOC
mamlaat	O
chota	O
uae	B-LOC
aur	O
russia	B-LOC
magar	O
par	O
agreement	O
thi	O
thi	O
ab	O
gaya	O
aman	O
sau	O
ka	O
us	O
russia	B-LOC
kal	O
alatifaq	O
wahan	O
state	O
zyada	O
usa	B-LOC
un	O
bhi	O
nato	B-ORG
resolution	O
naya	O
lakh	O
secretary	O
affairs	O
india	B-LOC
peace	O
honay	O
to	O
muahida	O
kiya	O
hazar	O
yahan	O
to	O
se	O
ne	O
alliance	O
nuclear	O
un	O
ki	O
bara	O
chota	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
ab	O
resolution	O
char	O
saarc	B-ORG
pakistan	B-LOC
sanctions	O
bairoon	O
sulah	O
ka	O
saarc	B-ORG
agar	O
bura	O
mamlaat	O
sau	O
treaty	O
ko	O
bainul	O
nuclear	O
to	O
rahi	O
resolution	O
rahe	O
general	O
uae	B-LOC
uk	B-LOC
honay	O
aqwam	O
acha	O
affairs	O
chota	O
kam	O
sanctions	O
intifada	O
uae	B-LOC
raha	O
aqwam	O
gayi	O
magar	O
islamabad	B-LOC
yahan	O
peace	O
keh	O
council	O
aqwam	O
jangi	O
kuch	O
panch	O
affairs	O
afghanistan	B-LOC
state	O
mamlaat	O
gaya	O
naya	O
hain	O
ab	O
diplomacy	O
wahan	O
summit	O
uk	B-LOC
hai	O
bahut	O
ne	O
embassy	O
intifada	O
border	O
ajlasa	O
jo	O
hai	O
roznamcha	O
nuclear	O
pakistan	B-LOC
rahi	O
baqiyat	O
lakh	O
roznamcha	O
gaya	O
refugee	O
cooperation	O
council	O
visit	O
islamabad	B-LOC
ek	O
gayi	O
nato	B-ORG
refugee	O
bura	O
asean	O
kuch	O
char	O
bara	O
sab	O
se	O
rahi	O
zyada	O
talks	O
negotiations	O
wahan	O
rahi	O
mamlaat	O
tha	O
wahan	O
crisis	O
lekin	O
bahut	O
ke	O
uae	B-LOC
gaye	O
iran	B-LOC
tab	O
aur	O
negotiations	O
magar	O
panch	O
bilateral	O
alliance	O
usa	B-LOC
asean	O
par	O
ambassador	O

welfare	O
hazar	O
clinic	O
hai	O
ya	O
thi	O
mein	O
heart	O
char	O
taleem	O
teen	O
polio	O
dengue	O
kiya	O
mein	O
bahut	O
pakistan	B-LOC
gaya	O
gayi	O
is	O
par	O
community	O
dawa	O
ke	O
school	O
ek	O
ne	O
teacher	O
naya	O
keh	O
literacy	O
lekin	O
lahore	B-LOC
sau	O
ek	O
paani	O
bura	O
do	O
chota	O
malaria	O
aur	O
diabetes	O
ki	O
chota	O
nutrition	O
madrasa	O
mein	O
polio	O
wahan	O
student	O
honay	O
water	O
mental	O
ngo	O
lekin	O
chota	O
hazar	O
unicef	B-ORG
clinic	O
community	O
bara	O
who	B-ORG
hain	O
raha	O
honay	O
us	O
bahut	O
hospital	O
polio	O
patient	O
hai	O
bara	O
zyada	O
community	O
is	O
jab	O
unicef	B-ORG
patient	O
gaya	O
thi	O
shagird	O
heart	O
clinic	O
qoum	O
bara	O
rehan	O
parhai	O
child	O
qoum	O
hai	O
heart	O
doctor	O
ustaad	O
university	O
keh	O
chota	O
water	O
crore	O
patient	O
ngo	O
lakh	O
zyada	O
treatment	O
phir	O
karachi	B-LOC
bara	O
woh	O
ghar	O
ngo	O
education	O
ko	O
tha	O
tha	O
se	O
education	O
lakh	O
rahi	O
ka	O
aur	O
wahan	O
mein	O
child	O
bahut	O
medicine	O
bahut	O
sarkardar	O
thi	O
ke	O
diabetes	O
acha	O
ngo	O
social	O
welfare	O
kal	O
woh	O
yeh	O
kal	O
dengue	O
college	O
relief	O
kam	O
magar	O
us	O
shelter	O
scholarship	O
university	O
khwateen	O
hazar	O
is	O
hain	O
school	O
malaria	O
school	O
acha	O
khwateen	O
rehan	O
hain	O
ko	O
medicine	O
covid	O
agar	O
woh	O
relief	O
rahi	O
nay	O
to	O
gayi	O
yeh	O
sewage	O
bahut	O
cancer	O
hospital	O
shagird	O
nay	O
vaccine	O
medicine	O
keh	O
diabetes	O
jo	O
college	O
gaye	O
hospital	O
vaccine	O
phir	O
insaan	O
zyada	O
mein	O
paani	O
curriculum	O
treatment	O
ki	O
development	O
university	O
honay	O
